I call it a hit.
我称之为打击。
- What'll your review say? VALET: Car, sir?
- 你的评论会说什么？ - 车，先生？
I like it too, so I guess I'll pan it.
我也喜欢这个， 所以我想我会平移它。
That's logical.
这是合乎逻辑的。
My publisher resents Cohan impersonating the president of the United States.
我的出版商讨厌 Cohan 冒充 美国的总统。
Says our young readers dream of being president.
说我们的年轻读者梦想 成为总统。
"I'd rather be right than be president."
“我宁愿是对的 而不是当总统。”
Cohan may find out he isn't either one.
科汉可能会发现 他不是其中之一。
I don't see how George does it at his age.
我不明白乔治是怎么做到的 在他这个年纪。
I remember him when he was a little boy.
我记得他 当他还是个小男孩的时候。
MAN: Congratulations, George, old boy. You did a great job.
祝贺你，乔治，老男孩。 你做的非常出色。
- Thanks. Thanks very much. WOMAN: Congratulations.
- 谢谢。非常感谢。 - 恭喜。
- You had him down to a tee. - We're still treading on dangerous ground.
- 你把他逼到了发球台。 - 我们仍然在危险的土地上行走。
Imitating the president, a lot of people aren't gonna like it.
模仿总统， 很多人不会喜欢它。
It's all good, clean fun. Didn't they enjoy it in Boston?
一切都很好，干净有趣。 他们在波士顿不喜欢吗？
- Never could do anything wrong in Boston. - Ha-ha-ha!
- 在波士顿永远不会做错任何事。 - 哈哈哈！
Greatest man in the United States played by the greatest actor.
美国最伟大的人 由最伟大的演员扮演。
Nothing wrong with that, especially when the greatest actor is my husband.
没有错，尤其是 当最伟大的演员是我的丈夫。
- This could be treason. - Don't worry.
- 这可能是叛国罪。 - 不用担心。
I know a dollar-a-year man who'll take care of you.
我认识一个年薪一美元的人 谁来照顾你。
- A lot would like to shoot actors. - Save these telegrams.
- 很多想拍演员。 - 保存这些电报。
The government needs paper.
政府需要纸。
You've got a list like who's who here. There's everybody but Hirohito.
你有一个列表，比如这里的谁是谁。 除了裕仁之外，其他人都在。
- We'll bring him in on a shutter. - Here's mine.
- 我们会用百叶窗把他带进来。 - 这是我的。
- Won't you read all that cleverness? - What makes you think I didn't?
- 你不会读所有的聪明吗？ - 是什么让你认为我没有？
I didn't know there was that much love left in the entire Western Union codebook.
我不知道有那么多爱 留在整个西联汇款密码本中。
PHOTOGRAPHER: Hold that. Thank you. SAM: Uh-oh.
- 坚持下去。谢谢你。 - 哦哦。
- Don't bother me. - It's from the White House.
- 不要打扰我。 - 来自白宫。
- That bothers me. - Here.
- 这让我很困扰。 - 这里。
You read it, Sam. These aren't my reading glasses. What's it say?
你读过它，山姆。这些不是 我的老花镜。它说什么？
"George M. Cohan, the Alvin Theater, New York.
“乔治·M·科汉， 纽约阿尔文剧院。
The president of the U.S. requests that you call upon him...
美国总统要求 你叫他……
...at your earliest convenience in regard to a personal matter.
...在您方便的时候尽早 关于个人的事情。
Kindly reply for definite appointment at White House.
请回复确定预约 在白宫。
Steven T. Early, secretary to the president."
史蒂文·T·早期， 总统的秘书。”
GEORGE: Hmm.
唔。
There you are, Sam.
你来了，山姆。
There you are. What did I tell you?
你在这。我跟你说了什么？
Coming at a time like this, with everything he has on his mind...
在这样的时刻到来， 带着他心中所想的一切……
...this is not just a casual invitation.
...这不仅仅是一个 随意的邀请。
This is important.
这个很重要。
- I think we're in trouble. - Don't worry.
- 我想我们有麻烦了。 - 不用担心。
They don't telegraph you to come and be shot at sunrise.
他们不会电你来 并在日出时被枪杀。
He doesn't get up that early.
他不会起那么早。
Besides, I've got a run-of-the-play contract. Fine time to make lame jokes. Hmm.
此外，我还有一份完整的合同。 开蹩脚笑话的好时机。唔。
I'm worried, Sam. I'm really worried.
我很担心，山姆。我真的很担心。
GUARD: Halt!
停！
- Yes, sir. What can I do for you? - I've got an appointment.
- 是的先生。我能为你做什么？ - 我有约会。
- And the name, please? - Cohan. George M. Cohan.
- 请问名字？ - 科汉。乔治·M·科汉。
All right, sir, if you'll wait just one moment, I'll call.
好的，先生，如果您等一下 稍等一下，我会打电话的。
Sergeant Lewis at the Pennsylvania Avenue gate.
刘易斯中士 在宾夕法尼亚大道门口。
- Good evening, Mr. Cohan. - Good evening.
- 晚上好，科汉先生。 - 晚上好。
- We've been expecting you. - Thank you.
- 我们一直在等你。 - 谢谢。
Why, your coat's wet. Didn't you come in the car?
为什么，你的外套湿了。 你没上车吗？
No, I walked up from the station.
不，我从车站走上来。
Washington's a great town to walk in. I always get a kick out of it.
华盛顿是一个很适合步行的小镇。 我总是从中获得乐趣。
Yes, indeed. Won't you come with me?
确实是的。 你不跟我来吗？
I was supposed to be off-duty this evening, Mr. Cohan...
我应该下班 今晚，科汉先生...
...but when I heard you was coming, I thought...
...但是当我听说你要来的时候， 我想...
...I would like to see if you looked the same.
...我想看看 如果你看起来一样。
That depends just on when you saw me last.
那只取决于 在你最后一次见到我的时候。
Well, it must have been 30-some years ago.
嗯，应该是 30 多年前。
I was valet for Mr. Teddy Roosevelt.
我是泰迪·罗斯福先生的代客。
He got me a seat up in the gallery.
他让我在画廊里坐了下来。
The play was George Washington, Jr.
这出戏是小乔治华盛顿。
And you was just singing and dancing all about the grand old flag.
而你只是唱歌跳舞 所有关于宏伟的旧国旗。
Mr. Teddy used to sing it in his bathtub.
泰迪先生曾经唱歌 它在他的浴缸里。
- It was a good old song in its day. - Yes, sir, it was...
- 这是一首好听的老歌。 - 是的，先生，那是……
...and it's just as good today as it ever was.
...今天也一样好 一如既往。
PRESIDENT: Come in.
进来。
Well, hello there.
嗯，你好。
- How's my double? - Your double isn't any too sure.
- 我的替身怎么样？ - 你的替身不太确定。
Give me time to work on that one.
给我时间做那个。
Why, I was told you knew all the answers.
为什么，有人告诉我你知道 所有的答案。
There was a time when I thought so. Right now, I wish I did.
有一段时间我是这么想的。 现在，我希望我做到了。
Yes, so do I. Sit down, Mr. Cohan.
是的，我也是。坐下，科汉先生。
Thanks.
谢谢。
- You know, I'm a little bit nervous. - Heh-heh-heh.
- 你知道，我有点紧张。 - 嘿嘿嘿。
I'm sorry I missed the opening of your show.
对不起，我错过了开幕式 你的节目。
Maybe just as well.
也许也一样。
Don't worry about it. We understand each other perfectly.
别担心。 我们非常了解对方。
- I think so. - The Herald Tribune says...
- 我认同。 - 先驱论坛报说……
...that you make a better president and I'd rather be right than I am.
...你会成为一个更好的总统 我宁愿做对也不愿做对。
Don't forget, that's a Republican newspaper.
别忘了， 那是一份共和党报纸。
I can remember you and your family very well. The Four Cohans.
我记得你和你的家人 很好。四个科汉。
Do you, really, Mr. President? That's a long time ago.
总统先生，你真的吗？ 那是很久以前的事了。
Yes. It was while I was attending school near Boston.
是的。那是我的时候 在波士顿附近上学。
I was a pretty cocky kid those days.
那些日子我是个很自大的孩子。
Pretty cocky kid. A regular Yankee Doodle Dandy.
好自大的孩子。 一个普通的洋基涂鸦花花公子。
Always carrying a flag in a parade or following one.
总是带着旗帜 在游行或跟随。
- I hope you haven't outgrown the habit. - Not a chance.
- 我希望你没有养成这个习惯。 - 没有机会。
That's one thing I always admired about you Irish-Americans.
这是我一直钦佩的一件事 关于你们爱尔兰裔美国人。
You carry your love of country like a flag, right out in the open.
你带着你对祖国的热爱 像一面旗帜，就在外面。
It's a great quality.
这是一个伟大的品质。
I inherited that, got that from my father.
我继承了那个， 从我父亲那里得到的。
He ran away to the Civil War when he was 13.
他逃到内战 在他 13 岁的时候。
Proudest kid in the state of Massachusetts.
全州最骄傲的孩子 马萨诸塞州。
So you've spent your life telling the other 47 states...
所以你度过了你的一生 告诉其他 47 个州...
...what a great country it is.
......这是一个多么伟大的国家。
I never thought of it just that way before...
我从来没想过 以前就是这样...
...but I guess that's about the size of it.
……但我猜 这大约是它的大小。
And I lost no time, either.
我也没有浪费时间。
It started with a very funny incident, about 60 years ago.
从一个非常有趣的事件开始， 大约60年前。
It was in Providence, Rhode Island, on the Fourth of July.
那是在罗德岛普罗维登斯， 七月四日。
There weren't so many stars then, in the flag or on the stage...
那时候还没有那么多明星 在旗帜上或舞台上...
...but folks knew that more were coming.
...但人们知道 更多的人来了。
They were optimistic, happy and expectant.
他们乐观， 快乐和期待。
The beginning of the Horatio Alger Age.
的开始 霍雷肖阿尔及尔时代。
My father was playing in a variety, breaking in a single.
我父亲在玩各种游戏， 破单。
Nobody was more expectant than he was...
没有人更期待 比他...
...unless it was my mother.
……除非是我妈妈。
She was busy right then on a smaller production.
她当时很忙 在较小的生产上。
[SINGING] Larry O'Leary is me name
拉里·奥利里是我的名字
By trade I am a dancing master
通过交易，我是一名舞蹈大师
There's no one can teach the same
没有人可以教相同的
Nor teach it any faster
也不会教得更快
It's easy, very easy
这很容易，非常容易
If you watch every twist, every turn
如果你观察每一个转折，每一个转折
Keep your eyes upon me And surprised you will be
让你的眼睛注视着我 你会很惊讶
At the dancing you have yet to learn
在跳舞时你还没有学会
Keep your eyes upon me And surprised you will be
让你的眼睛注视着我 你会很惊讶
At the dancing you have yet to learn
在跳舞时你还没有学会
- Any messages come for me? - Not yet.
- 有消息找我吗？ - 还没有。
- Better take a bow, Jerry. - Can't. I gotta leave.
- 最好鞠躬，杰瑞。 - 不能。我得走了。
MAX: Watch that water! - Max, I gotta leave.
- 看那水！ - 麦克斯，我得走了。
- I gotta find out what's happening. - Oh, for heaven's sake, Jerry.
- 我得弄清楚发生了什么事。 - 哦，看在上帝的份上，杰瑞。
Take up Number 3. You're on. Go ahead. Light's up.
占据第 3 位。 轮到你了。前进。点亮。
- Bye, Sally. - Good luck.
- 再见，莎莉。 - 祝你好运。
You can't run through the streets in that outfit.
你不能穿过街道 穿着那件衣服。
- They'll put you in jail. - Have to catch me first.
- 他们会把你关进监狱。 - 必须先抓住我。
Don't forget, Jerry, you're on again at 4: 15.
别忘了，杰瑞， 4:15 你又开始了。
- Don't worry. I'll be back. - These things take hours sometimes.
- 不用担心。我会回来的。 - 这些事情有时需要几个小时。
My wife never held up a show in her life.
我的妻子从不坚持 她生命中的一场表演。
JERRY: Excuse me, can I get through here?
打扰一下，我可以通过这里吗？
The Irish are at the head of the parade.
爱尔兰人在 游行的负责人。
- I'm not in the parade. I want to get through. - Not a chance, brother.
- 我不参加游行。我想通过。 - 没有机会，兄弟。
You don't say so. We'll get you there in a jiffy!
你不这么说。 我们很快就会把你送到那里！
Here, this'll give you courage. Charge!
在这里，这会给 你的勇气。收费！
Nellie.
内莉。
- Is she all right? - She's doing fine.
- 她没事吧？ - 她过得很好。
- What is it? - Well, all signs point to its being a boy.
- 它是什么？ - 好吧，所有迹象都表明它是个男孩。
Wait. He just got here and he's sleeping already.
等待。他刚到 他已经在睡觉了。
All babies sleep 20 hours a day, Jerry.
所有婴儿都睡 20 每天几个小时，杰瑞。
That's why most of them never amount to anything.
这就是为什么他们中的大多数 永远不会有任何意义。
- What'll we call him? - Oh, I don't know.
- 我们叫他什么？ - 哦，我不知道。
- What do you say? - Well, seeing that he arrived...
- 你说什么？ - 好吧，看到他来了……
...on the Fourth of July, what about George Washington Cohan?
……七月四日， 乔治华盛顿科汉呢？
Well, it has a nice patriotic ring to it. What do you think?
嗯，它有一个很好的爱国戒指。 你怎么看？
Oh, the George is fine, but the Washington...
哦，乔治很好， 但是华盛顿...
...may be too long for a billboard.
...对于广告牌来说可能太长了。
Well, how about a nice short Irish name? Dennis or Michael?
那么，一个漂亮的爱尔兰短名字怎么样？ 丹尼斯还是迈克尔？
George Michael Cohan. Heh.
乔治·迈克尔·科汉。呵呵。
Yes, I like that name.
是的，我喜欢这个名字。
Oh, gosh. I forgot.
哦，天哪。我忘了。
Hey! It's a boy!
嘿！是个男孩！
Oh, Jerry.
哦，杰瑞。
Heavenly day, Nellie! He's crying with a brogue.
天堂般的日子，内莉！ 他正在用布洛克鞋哭泣。
GEORGE: The first thing I ever had my fist on was the American flag.
我拥有的第一件事 拳头是美国国旗。
I hitched my wagon to 38 stars and 13 stripes.
我把我的马车搭到 38 星星和 13 条条纹。
I was 6 or 7 years old before I realized they weren't celebrating my birthday...
在我意识到之前，我是 6 或 7 岁 他们没有庆祝我的生日...
...on the Fourth of July.
……七月四日。
Then my folks had a real break...
然后我的家人真的休息了......
...when my little sister Josie made her entrance.
...当我的小妹妹乔西 让她进入。
She grew to love show business...
她渐渐爱上了演艺界……
...just as she loved everybody and everything.
......就像她爱每个人一样 和所有。
We toured the kerosene circuit in a tank show...
我们参观了煤油电路 在坦克表演...
...called Daniel Boone on the Trail.
...在小路上打电话给丹尼尔布恩。
Everybody doubled in brass. Dad walloped the bass drum.
每个人都在黄铜中翻了一番。 爸爸敲了敲大鼓。
For some reason, they teamed me with a donkey.
由于某些原因， 他们把我和一头驴子联合起来。
I was a good Democrat even in those days.
我是个好民主党人 即使在那些日子。
Mother and Josie threw out handbills.
妈妈和乔西扔了传单。
Their smiles would've sold tickets to wooden Indians.
他们的微笑会卖票 给木头印第安人。
They kept putting new stars on the flag...
他们不断推出新的 国旗上的星星...
...and the Cohans kept rushing out to meet them.
......科汉一家一直冲出去 去见他们。
We had jokes to match every cornfield. We sang at every milk station.
我们有笑话来匹配每一个玉米地。 我们在每个牛奶站唱歌。
[SINGING] Larry O'Leary is me name
拉里·奥利里是我的名字
By trade, I am a dancing master
通过贸易，我是舞蹈大师
There's no one can teach the same
没有人可以教相同的
Or teach it
或者教它
Any faster
更快
It's easy, very easy
这很容易，非常容易
If you watch every twist, every turn
如果你观察每一个转折，每一个转折
Keep your eyes upon me And surprised you will be
让你的眼睛注视着我 你会很惊讶
At the dancing you have yet to learn
在跳舞时你还没有学会
Keep your eyes upon me And surprised you will be
让你的眼睛注视着我 你会很惊讶
At the dancing you have yet to learn
在跳舞时你还没有学会
[SINGING] I was taken by surprise
我被吓到了
By a pair of roguish eyes
被一双恶毒的眼睛
While strolling through the park one day
漫步时 公园一日
GEORGE: We trouped through depression and inflation, the country's growing pains.
我们在抑郁症和 通货膨胀，国家成长的阵痛。
Froze in winter and roasted in summer.
冬天结冰 并在夏天烤。
But it was a good life.
但这是一个美好的生活。
It's a lucky family that dances together every day.
这是一个幸运的家庭 每天一起跳舞。
1891 found our fortunes flat as a pancake.
1891 年找到了我们的财富 像煎饼一样平。
Then came a bolt from the blue, jobs for the whole family...
然后，晴天霹雳， 全家人的工作...
...in a show called Peck's Bad Boy.
...在一个名为派克的坏男孩的节目中。
We opened in Brooklyn. Heh-heh-heh.
我们在布鲁克林开业。呵呵呵。
The town was known for its spirited audiences even before it had a ball team.
这个小镇以其充满活力而闻名 观众甚至在它有一支球队之前。
JERRY: Who keeps hammering on our opening night?
谁一直在锤 在我们的开幕之夜？
- What are you doing here? - I'm the star, ain't I?
- 你在这里做什么？ - 我是明星，不是吗？
You have the leading part, yes.
你有主角，是的。
That means I'm a star, and there should be a star...
这意味着我是明星 应该有一颗星星...
...on my dressing room door. That's the law of the theater.
...在我的更衣室门上。 这就是剧院的法则。
Yes, Jerry, give the devil his due.
是的，杰瑞，给魔鬼应得的。
I know, but I'm nervous. I'll go blank. I won't be able to remember a line.
我知道，但我很紧张。我会空白的。 我将无法记住一行。
Don't worry, Dad.
别担心，爸爸。
If you stick, I'll throw you a line. And you too, mother.
如果你坚持，我会扔给你一条线。 你也是，妈妈。
SCHULTS: Oh! Thief! Thief! Out! Out!
哦！贼！贼！出去！出去！
SCHULTS: Why do you do this to me?
你为什么要这样对我？
COP: It's to jail you're going, me boy!
你要去监狱，我的孩子！
JERRY: There, there, there, now. Henry's not really a bad boy.
那里，那里，那里，现在。 亨利并不是一个真正的坏孩子。
He's just mischievous, that's all.
他只是淘气，仅此而已。
Mr. Schults, I think that should take care of the damage. Don't you think?
舒尔茨先生，我认为应该小心 的损害。你不觉得吗？
Henry, I want you to promise the cop and Mr. Schults...
亨利，我要你保证 警察和舒尔茨先生...
...that from now on you'll always be a good boy.
……从现在开始 你永远是个好孩子。
I'll promise, but I can still lick any kid in town!
我保证， 但我仍然可以舔镇上的任何孩子！
- Fine work, Georgie. NELLIE: I'm proud of you.
- 干得好，乔治。 - 我以你为荣。
- Great, Georgie, great. - Nice going, kid.
- 太好了，乔治，太好了。 - 进展顺利，孩子。
- Real piece of acting there, Georgie. - You're going places.
- 真正的表演，乔治。 - 你要去的地方。
- Boy, he sure rolled them in the aisles. - Thanks.
- 男孩，他肯定把它们滚到过道上。 - 谢谢。
But what are you all so surprised about?
但是你们都是什么 这么惊讶？
You could've told during rehearsals that I'd be a sensation.
你可以在排练时告诉 我会引起轰动。
Listen, there's nothing to this acting business.
听着，什么都没有 到这个演艺圈。
I wonder what took me so long to become a star.
我想知道是什么花了我这么长时间 成为明星。
Excuse me. Hey, Vance.
打扰一下。嘿，万斯。
Call a rehearsal for 10:00 tomorrow morning.
要求排练 明天早上10:00。
Jerry, the time has come for George's first spanking.
杰瑞，时间到了 乔治第一次打屁股。
That's right. I'll hold him while you hit him.
这是正确的。 你打他的时候我会抱着他。
Not me. I don't hit hard enough to make an impression.
不是我。我打得不够狠 给人留下深刻印象。
I can't do it. He'd think I'm jealous because he got more laughs than I did.
我做不到。他会认为我嫉妒 因为他比我笑得更多。
Don't think I'm not, either.
不要以为我也不是。
Uh, several gentlemen to see you outside, Mr. Cohan.
几位先生 到外面见你，科汉先生。
Oh.
哦。
Gentlemen of the press, I presume?
新闻界的先生们，我猜？
It's started already. Will you excuse me?
它已经开始了。 你会原谅我吗？
KID: Let's see how tough he is!
让我们看看他有多强悍！
GEORGE [SCREAMING]: Ow! Ow! Ow!
哦！哦！哦！
Ought to be arrested, every one of those hoodlums.
应该被逮捕 每一个流氓。
It seems to me you're taking all this very calmly, Jerry Cohan.
在我看来你正在服用 这一切都非常平静，杰里科汉。
Your own son almost murdered in cold blood.
你自己的儿子几乎 被冷血杀害。
Well, the way I figure, it's a fine tribute to Georgie's acting.
嗯，按照我的理解，这是一个 向乔治的表演致敬。
The way he plays the part, every kid will want to take a punch...
他扮演角色的方式， 每个孩子都会想打一拳……
...at Peck's bad boy just to see what happens.
...在派克的坏男孩 只是想看看会发生什么。
What?! Have I got to go through that every night?
什么？！我得走了吗 每晚都通过那个？
Yes. And matinees Wednesdays and Saturdays.
是的。还有周三的日场 和星期六。
Georgie, those boys did you a great favor...
乔治，那些男孩做了 你是一个很大的恩惠...
...and they saved me a lot of trouble.
...他们救了 我很麻烦。
You know, most actors give their whole lives to their profession, not once scoring a hit.
你知道，大多数演员都献出了自己的一生 对他们的职业来说，没有一次得分。
You're lucky. You're a hit at the age of 13.
你很幸运。 你在 13 岁时就很受欢迎。
I've been in this business a long time and never met a performer...
我从事这个行业很长时间了 从来没有遇到过表演者...
...who, in the long run, wouldn't rather be a great guy than a great actor.
...谁，从长远来看，宁愿 做一个伟大的人，而不是一个伟大的演员。
That is, until I made your acquaintance.
也就是说，直到我做出 你的熟人。
Can't I be both?
我不能两者兼而有之吗？
Chances are, the way you're going, you won't be either.
很有可能，你要走的路， 你也不会。
If the hoodlums don't get you, a committee of actors will.
如果流氓没有抓到你， 一个行动者委员会将。
Actors are considered a very bad risk by insurance companies.
演员被认为是非常糟糕的 保险公司的风险。
And any actor with a conceit like yours...
和任何有 像你一样自负...
...well, we just couldn't afford the premium.
......好吧，我们只是不能 承担溢价。
What your father really means is you're too sensitive.
你父亲的真正意思 是不是你太敏感了。
You're too anxious to make good.
你太急于做好事了。
You love the theater too much.
你太爱剧院了。
Oh, I know you can improve, if you want to.
哦，我知道你可以改进， 如果你想。
Sure, I can. Just watch me.
我当然可以。只是看着我。
From now on I'm Peck's bad boy only from 8:30 till 11 in the evening.
从现在开始我就是派克的坏孩子 仅从晚上 8:30 到 11 点。
- That's a boy, Georgie. - I promise, Mother.
- 那是个男孩，乔治。 - 我保证，妈妈。
And don't forget Wednesdays and Saturdays, 2:30 till 5.
别忘了星期三 和星期六，2:30 到 5。
Yes, sir! And the other 21 and a half hours, I pattern myself after dad.
是的先生！而另外的 21 个半 小时，我模仿爸爸。
Heh-heh. Well, you could find a better example...
呵呵。嗯，你可以找到 一个更好的例子...
...but that's the general idea.
...但这是一般的想法。
Jerry, what do you know. Ed Albee's coming backstage to see you.
杰瑞，你知道什么。 Ed Albee 要到后台来看你。
JERRY: Albee. - That's B.F. Keys' partner!
- 阿尔比。 - 那是 B.F. Keys 的搭档！
He's big-time vaudeville. We're in the big time.
他是个大名鼎鼎的杂耍演员。 我们正处于大时代。
He didn't send for us. He's come here to see us.
他没有派我们来。 他是来看我们的。
Maybe it'd be better if I spoke business to him.
也许会更好 如果我和他谈生意。
Georgie, I thought you said you were going to reform.
乔治，我以为你说 你要改革。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
When he comes in here, I want you to keep quiet.
当他进来的时候， 我要你保持安静。
Look at the condition of this room.
看看这个房间的状况。
Josie, get the cheap makeup off the table.
乔西，便宜点 化妆离开桌子。
Hurry up!
赶快！
JOSIE: Quick, Georgie!
快点，乔治！
Get the stuff off that shelf there. That's right.
把东西从那里的架子上拿下来。 这是正确的。
Hey, Albee'll be right in.
嘿，阿尔比马上就进来。
He just stopped at the water cooler.
他只是停在饮水机旁。
Jerry, if he offers you a cigar, don't take it.
杰瑞，如果他给你一支雪茄， 不要拿它。
I'll take it. That'll impress him if he thinks I can smoke.
我要买它。这会让他印象深刻 如果他认为我可以抽烟。
You get behind that curtain. Hurry up!
你躲在窗帘后面。 赶快！
I don't want to hear a word out of you. I don't even want to hear you breathe.
我不想听到你的话。 我什至不想听到你的呼吸声。
Josie, fix the chairs. The other one.
乔西，把椅子修好。另一个。
Here, take this. Oh, Jerry.
来，拿这个。哦，杰瑞。
- Sit down, Nellie. Sit down. - All right.
- 坐下，内莉。坐下。 - 好的。
Come in.
进来。
Mr. E.F. Albee.
E.F. 阿尔比先生。
- Hello, Cohan. JERRY: Mr. Albee.
- 你好，科汉。 - 阿尔比先生。
- Meet Mrs. Cohan. - How do you do?
- 认识科汉夫人。 - 你好吗？
NELLIE: How do you do? - Sit down.
- 坐下。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I saw your show tonight. Not bad.
我今晚看了你的节目。不错。
Have a cigar?
有根烟？
Uh, no, thanks.
呃，不，谢谢。
Your show is no good for vaudeville...
你的节目不好看 对于杂耍...
...but I've seen a lot worse right here in Brooklyn.
......但我见过更糟糕的 就在布鲁克林这里。
We're opening a new theater in Philadelphia...
我们要开一个新剧院 在费城...
...the Bijou, on the Fourth of July.
...比茹，七月四日。
If you can fix up a good vaudeville act, we'll double your present salary...
如果你能搞定一个好的杂耍表演， 我们会加倍你现在的薪水...
...give you 10 weeks' guarantee, and third or fourth billing.
...给你10周的保证， 和第三次或第四次计费。
- Double our salary? - You'll be with the best in the country.
- 我们的工资翻倍？ - 你会和全国最好的人在一起。
Vesta Victoria, Eddie Foy, Warren Volk, Charlie Case...
灶神星维多利亚，埃迪福伊， 沃伦·沃尔克、查理·凯斯……
Just a second.
等一下。
I'm George M. Cohan.
我是乔治·M·科汉。
You're opening a theater in Philadelphia on July 4th?
你要开剧院 7 月 4 日在费城？
- Yes, that's right. - That's my birthday.
- 是的，这是正确的。 - 那是我的生日。
Heh. Well, that isn't why we're opening the theater.
呵呵。嗯，这不是为什么 我们要开剧院了。
The salary's all right, but how have you got the nerve...
工资还行 但是你怎么有勇气...
...to offer us third or fourth billing after my performance tonight?
...为我们提供第三次或第四次计费 在我今晚的表演之后？
Is this kid in your show?
这个孩子在你的节目中吗？
Am I in the show?!
我在剧中吗？！
Who do you think was Peck's bad boy?
你认为谁是派克的坏孩子？
Oh, I beg your pardon. I didn't quite recognize you.
哦，对不起。 我没有完全认出你。
You didn't? Then maybe you're not the showman you're cracked up to be.
你没有？那么也许你不是 你被吹捧成的表演者。
NELLIE AND JERRY: George!
乔治！
Well, now, maybe I'm not.
好吧，现在，也许我不是。
Maybe you're not quite ready for the big time yet.
也许你还没有准备好 大的时候了。
Mrs. Cohan. Mr. Cohan. Good night.
科汉夫人。科汉先生。晚安。
NELLIE: Good night. JERRY: Uh, Mr. Albee.
- 晚安。 - 呃，阿尔比先生。
- How do you do, Mr. Albee? MAN: Good evening.
- 你好吗，阿尔比先生？ - 晚上好。
- Call you a carriage? - If you will.
- 叫你马车？ - 如果你愿意。
Carriage for Mr. Albee!
阿尔比先生的马车！
See what happens because you wouldn't lay a hand on him all these years?
看看会发生什么，因为你不会 这么多年来一直对他下手？
A mother isn't supposed to punish. She just gives her permission.
母亲不应该惩罚。 她只是允许。
Have I your permission?
我得到你的许可了吗？
- You certainly have. JERRY: Ahem.
- 你当然有。 - 咳咳。
Don't you ought to get my permission too, Dad?
你不应该得到 我也同意了，爸爸？
NELLIE: Not the hand! He plays the violin.
不是手！他拉小提琴。
All right, not on the hand.
好吧，不在手上。
Not on the mouth! He has to sing.
不上嘴！他必须唱歌。
All right, not on the mouth. Come here.
好吧，不是在嘴上。 过来。
Here's one place without any talent!
这是一个没有任何天赋的地方！
[SCREAMING] Ow! Ow! Ow!
哦！哦！哦！
- Who were Lewis and Clark, George? - Acrobats?
- 谁是路易斯和克拉克，乔治？ - 杂技演员？
Look at this swell write-up we got in the clipper.
看看这篇精彩的文章 我们上了快船。
GEORGE: You'd find us wherever new states sprouted on the prairie.
你会在任何新地方找到我们 州在草原上萌芽。
We played every town in America that had a theater.
我们玩遍了美国的每一个城镇 那有一个剧院。
Any mail for Mr. Cohan?
有科汉先生的邮件吗？
No. Your father picked up his mail.
不，你父亲收到了他的邮件。
I mean, for Mr. George M. Cohan.
我的意思是，对于 George M. Cohan 先生。
The next 10 years rushed by like a circus train.
下一个10年匆匆而过 像马戏团的火车一样。
Dad seemed content with the sticks, but I was straining at the leash.
爸爸似乎对棍子很满意， 但我拉紧了皮带。
Here's your mail, Mr. Cohan.
这是你的邮件，科汉先生。
Oh, thanks. A couple of tickets for the show.
哦谢谢。 几张演出门票。
We played stock in Buffalo.
我们在布法罗玩股票。
Being versatile, I was playing my mother's father.
多才多艺， 我在扮演我母亲的父亲。
NELLIE: Oh, Daddy, he has left me.
哦，爸爸，他离开了我。
GEORGE: All is for the best, my daughter.
一切都是最好的，我的女儿。
In life, we trip, but right ourselves.
在生活中，我们旅行， 但我们自己。
I was correct about man's love.
我对男人的爱是正确的。
First, he considers his pleasure or his honor or his purse.
首先，他认为他的快乐 或他的荣誉或他的钱包。
And only secondly does he think of the woman he says he loves.
其次，他认为 他说他爱的女人。
Now I must go life's journey alone...
现在我必须独自踏上人生的旅途……
...and struggle on my weary way to find peace.
...在我疲倦的路上挣扎 寻找和平。
Courage, Emily, courage.
勇气，艾米丽，勇气。
Living has taught your father many things.
生活教会了你 父亲很多事情。
Among them, to take the bitter with the better.
其中， 以更好的方式取苦。
The road to happiness is paved with heartaches and stones.
通往幸福的路已经铺好了 心痛和石头。
- Good luck, Josie. - Thanks, Mom.
- 祝你好运，乔西。 - 谢谢妈妈。
They're all yours, sweetheart.
他们都是你的，亲爱的。
Good luck, honey.
祝你好运，亲爱的。
Hey, George, there's a young lady, would like to talk to you.
嘿，乔治，有一位年轻女士， 想和你谈谈。
Show her in.
带她进去。
All right, Miss.
好的，小姐。
- Mr. Cohan will see you. - Thank you.
- 科汉先生会见你的。 - 谢谢。
He's all yours.
他都是你的。
I'm 18. I sing and I dance, and I'm going to New York.
我18岁。我唱歌跳舞， 我要去纽约。
Should I?
我是不是该？
Oh, Mr. Cohan, you're so old and so experienced in the theater.
哦，科汉先生，你太老了 所以在剧院经验丰富。
So fatherly.
太父爱了。
Do you think it's wise?
你认为这是明智的吗？
I mean, my being 18, singing and dancing, and going to New York?
我是说，我18岁，唱歌跳舞， 去纽约？
Well, ahem, that's very wise. I mean, being 18 is very wise.
嗯，嗯，这是非常明智的。 我的意思是，18岁是非常明智的。
And as for New York...
至于纽约……
...The Four Cohans open there this fall with their new show...
...四个科汉在那里开门 今年秋天与他们的新节目...
...with a new cyclorama and 2 carloads of scenery.
...带有一个新的环幕 和2车风景。
Really? When are you leaving here?
真的吗？你什么时候离开这里？
- Tomorrow night, right after the show. - Oh. I can't leave till Wednesday.
- 明天晚上，演出结束后。 - 哦。我要到星期三才能离开。
- I graduate from high school Tuesday. - Oh. That's too bad.
- 我周二高中毕业。 - 哦。这太糟糕了。
Oh, Georgie... Uh, excuse me.
哦，乔治……呃，对不起。
You haven't forgotten we have a date tonight?
你没有忘记 我们今晚有个约会？
Oh, no, no, no. Of course not.
哦，不，不，不。当然不是。
We're going roller-skating.
我们要去滑旱冰。
Roller-skating on a night like this?
在这样的夜晚滑旱冰？
Why, there's a moon out.
为什么，外面有一个月亮。
I'll be ready in five minutes.
我会在五分钟内准备好。
Pipperino, isn't she?
皮佩里诺，不是吗？
- Yes. Is she your daughter? - Oh, I'm not married.
- 是的。她是你的女儿吗？ - 哦，我还没结婚。
- Your niece, perhaps? - No, she's just a kid with the show.
- 你的侄女，也许？ - 不，她只是个表演节目的孩子。
We've been dating.
我们一直在约会。
Isn't she a little too young for you?
她对你来说是不是太年轻了点？
No. She's getting along in years. She's 17.
不，她相处得很好 多年。她17岁。
Well, shall I sing for you?
那么，我为你唱歌好吗？
I know I have talent, even if I am from Buffalo.
我知道我有才华， 即使我来自布法罗。
Well, we haven't got any piano handy.
好吧，我们手边没有钢琴。
Well, I'll dance.
好吧，我会跳舞。
GEORGE: Mm-hm. Ahem.
嗯嗯。咳咳。
Well, uh, that's rather old, isn't it?
嗯，那是相当古老的， 不是吗？
Everybody's done that. You don't want to be just an imitator, do you?
每个人都这样做了。你不想 只是一个模仿者，你呢？
Oh, no. Here's a step I made up myself.
不好了。 这是我自己编造的一个步骤。
But on the other hand...
但另一方面...
...you don't want to be too original either, do you?
......你不想太 原创的，你呢？
- No. - Well, I tell you what you do.
- 不。 - 好吧，我告诉你你做了什么。
You sit right here. You sit right here, and I will give you an idea of what I mean.
你坐在这里。你坐在这里，然后 我会让你明白我的意思。
It may not be much. I'm not the dancer I used to be, but then who is?
可能不多。我不是舞者 我曾经是，但后来是谁？
Now, watch carefully now.
现在，仔细观察。
Oh, no, no!
哦，不，不！
- Don't you like it? - Oh, but your heart!
- 你不喜欢吗？ - 哦，但你的心！
My heart is every bit as good as it ever was.
我的心是每一点 一如既往的好。
Oh, so fast!
哦，这么快！
Such excitement, at your age.
如此激动，在你这个年纪。
Sit down and rest.
坐下来休息。
Maybe I have overdone it a little.
也许我做得有点过头了。
Oh, look at the perspiration on your brow.
哦，看汗水 在你的额头上。
Your wrinkles. What happened to your wrinkles?
你的皱纹。 你的皱纹怎么了？
Well, I do have to make up older than I actually am, you know.
好吧，我确实必须弥补老 比我实际的，你知道的。
- How old are you? - Eh...
- 你今年多大？ - 呃……
Not yet 70.
还不到70。
You seem different from when I first came in.
你看起来不一样 从我刚进来的时候开始。
Even your voice sounds younger.
即使你的声音听起来更年轻。
Well, you see, it's a gift I have.
嗯，你看，这是我的礼物。
I'm always as young as the people I'm with...
我永远年轻 作为和我在一起的人...
...and you've made me feel very young.
......你已经做到了 我觉得自己很年轻。
- Very young. Heh-heh-heh. - I'm glad.
- 非常年轻。呵呵呵。 - 我很高兴。
Well, now, let's make plans.
好吧，现在，让我们制定计划。
Which manager should I take you to see first?
哪个经理 我要先带你去看看吗？
Uh, Klaw and Erlanger?
呃，克劳和厄兰格？
Good old Abe's a very nice fellow, but maybe a little bit too soon.
好老安倍是个很好的人， 但也许有点太早了。
Uh, Tony Pastor?
呃，托尼·帕斯特？
Well, that's better.
嗯，这样更好。
Albee, Coster, Beale, and Proctor...
阿尔比、科斯特、比尔和普洛克托……
- Oh! GEORGE: Huh?
- 哦！ - 嗯？
Wait a minute, little girl.
等一下，小姑娘。
You're not gonna let a beard and eyebrows frighten you, are you?
你不会留胡子的 眉毛让你害怕，是吗？
In show business, you'll see a lot of those.
在演艺界， 你会看到很多。
I'm not sure I want to go into show business now.
我不确定我想去 现在进入演艺圈。
With your talent and ability?
凭你的才华和能力？
There are very few around who can sing and dance and act too.
周围很少 会唱歌会跳舞会演戏的人。
How do you know I can do all those things? You've never seen me.
你怎么知道我可以做所有这些事情？ 你从来没有见过我。
I don't have to. I can tell a trouper a mile away, right on sight.
我不必。我可以告诉一个演员 一英里外，就在眼前。
I feel as though I've known you for years.
我感觉好像我已经 认识你多年。
- What's your name? - Mary.
- 你叫什么名字？ - 玛丽。
That's a very pretty name, a very pretty name. Now, Mary, you calm down.
这是一个非常漂亮的名字，非常 名字很好听。现在，玛丽，你冷静点。
Let's have a bite to eat, huh? I always eat after the last show.
让我们吃点东西，嗯？ 我总是在最后一场演出后吃饭。
- Are you hungry? - Yes.
- 你饿了吗？ - 是的。
I've been here since 2:00 this afternoon, trying to get up courage to come backstage.
我从今天下午 2:00 就到了这里， 试图鼓起勇气回到后台。
You must be hungry after seven shows.
七场演出后你一定饿了。
We'll have a nice cold bottle and a bird.
我们会好好感冒的 瓶子和一只鸟。
What's a cold bottle?
什么是冷瓶？
In show business we call that a piece of pie and a glass of milk.
在演艺界，我们称之为 一块馅饼和一杯牛奶。
Aren't you going roller-skating with that, tlick-tlick, Pipperino?
你不去滑旱冰吗 有了那个，滴答滴答，Pipperino？
Nah, I'm tired of picking her up.
不，我厌倦了接她。
- What's the matter, Mary? - Oh!
- 怎么了，玛丽？ - 哦！
Got it.
知道了。
ALL [SINGING]: I was born in Virginia
我出生在弗吉尼亚
That's the state that will win ya
那是会赢得你的状态
If you've got a soul in ya
如果你有灵魂
Ain't no southern frown
没有南方皱眉
WOMEN: In the city of Norfolk
在诺福克市
MEN: Home of beauties and war talk
美女之家和战争谈话
WOMEN: Reckon you'll like it MEN: If you should strike it
- 估计你会喜欢的 - 如果你应该打它
ALL: That doggone town
那个狗镇
Pretty good. There's a contract in my desk already made out.
非常好。有合同 在我的办公桌上已经做出来了。
Go and get it. Say.
去拿吧。说。
If any of the Cohans ask you how you like their act, just tell them it was fair.
如果任何一个科汉人问你喜欢什么 他们的行为，告诉他们这是公平的。
I get you.
我明白了。
Reckon you'll like it If you should strike it
估计你会喜欢的 如果你应该打击它
That doggone town
那个狗镇
Ladies and gentlemen...
女士们先生们...
...my mother thanks you...
...我妈妈谢谢你...
...my father thanks you...
...我父亲谢谢你...
...my sister thanks you...
……姐姐谢谢你……
...and I thank you.
......我谢谢你。
WOMAN: Nice going.
好走。
That's tearing them out of their chairs.
这让他们心碎 离开他们的椅子。
All set up for you, boys. Go get them.
男孩们，一切都为你准备好了。 去拿他们。
Oh, Dad, after the way we went tonight, we're certainly ready for New York.
哦，爸爸，在我们今晚走过的路之后， 我们当然已经为纽约做好了准备。
If we're a hit here, it's a cinch in New York.
如果我们在这里很受欢迎， 这在纽约是小菜一碟。
- Nice going, kid. - Thanks.
- 进展顺利，孩子。 - 谢谢。
Oh, uh, Mr. Cohan, just a minute.
哦，呃，科汉先生，请稍等。
- Pretty fair act you folks have got. - They seemed to like it.
- 你们得到了相当公平的行为。 - 他们似乎喜欢它。
That's a soft audience. Got any open time?
那是一个软听众。 有开放时间吗？
- Yes, from now on. - I'd like to make you an offer.
- 是的，从现在开始。 - 我想给你一个报价。
- We'd be glad to talk about it. - Fine. Fine. Heh.
- 我们很乐意谈论它。 - 美好的。美好的。呵呵。
You know, they're always a soft audience here on Wednesday. Pushover.
你知道，他们总是软弱的听众 星期三在这里。推倒。
- Oh. Mm-hm. - Did you catch it?
- 哦。嗯嗯。 - 你懂了吗？
Oh, you were wonderful, George.
哦，你太棒了，乔治。
- But I don't know. I miss that beard. - Uh-huh.
- 但我不知道。我想念那个胡子。 - 嗯。
- Did you get up on that number? - Yes. It's a lovely song, George.
- 你起床了吗？ - 是的。这是一首可爱的歌，乔治。
- I've learned it by heart. - Good.
- 我已经背诵了。 - 好的。
I did it with the orchestra leader, and you do it this show.
我和管弦乐队的领队一起做的， 你做这个节目。
He knows your key, and you just follow him for tempo.
他知道你的钥匙， 你只要跟着他的节奏就行了。
There's a notice on the call-board. You can't change your act after the first show.
呼叫板上有通知。你 第一次演出后不能改变你的行为。
The manager expects me to sing "The Wedding of the Lily and the Rose."
经理希望我唱歌 “百合与玫瑰的婚礼。”
Who were they applauding out there, the manager or me?
他们在外面为谁鼓掌， 经理还是我？
- Now, go on out there and do it. - Oh, George, I can't move.
- 现在，去那里做吧。 - 哦，乔治，我动不了了。
I can't go out there, not without rehearsal.
我不能出去， 不是没有排练。
What are you worried about?
你在担心什么？
You're doing a George M. Cohan lyric to a George M. Cohan melody.
你正在做一个乔治·M·科汉 George M. Cohan 旋律的歌词。
Yes, but it's my voice.
是的，但这是我的声音。
A George M. Cohan discovery. Nobody ever had a better start.
George M. Cohan 的发现。 没有人有过更好的开始。
There's your introduction. Go on.
有你的介绍。继续。
Good luck, kid.
祝你好运，孩子。
[SINGING] When they see it coming All them babies take a chill
当他们看到它的到来 他们所有的婴儿都感冒了
Diamonds glistening all around And style enough to kill
钻石闪耀四方 和风格足以杀死
Her steady fella broke a dice game Down in Louisville
她的稳重的家伙打破了骰子游戏 在路易斯维尔下来
And buys her chicken every day for lunch "Come seven"
每次都买她的鸡 午餐“七点”
Dreamy eyes that sparkle And she rolls them mighty cute
梦幻般的眼睛闪闪发光 她把它们卷起来非常可爱
Colored gentlemen say "That lady certainly is a beaut"
有色人君说 “那位小姐果然是个美女”
Go broke that she's a hot potato
破产吧，她是个烫手山芋
She's a red-hot radiator
她是炽热的散热器
She's the warmest baby in the bunch
她是这群人中最温暖的宝贝
Ten consecutive weeks in New York. That's the big time.
在纽约连续十周。 那是大时代。
When you leave New York, Philadelphia, Boston...
当你离开纽约时， 费城、波士顿……
- Let me take a look at that. - Excuse me.
- 让我看看那个。 - 打扰一下。
What's going on here? Take your makeup off.
这里发生了什么？ 卸妆。
I'll be back in just a minute.
我马上就回来。
MARY: Colored gentlemen say "That lady certainly is a beaut"
有色人君说 “那位小姐果然是个美女”
Go broke that she's a hot potato She's a red-hot radiator
破产吧，她是个烫手山芋 她是炽热的散热器
Hey, Bill. What is this? What's she singing?
嘿，比尔。这是什么？ 她在唱什么？
Who told her to switch that number?
谁让她换号码的？
She's supposed to sing "The Wedding of the Lily and the Rose."
她应该唱歌 “百合与玫瑰的婚礼。”
- Now, who told her to switch that number? - I don't know.
- 现在，谁让她换那个号码的？ - 我不知道。
You don't know?
你不知道吗？
Bring down that curtain!
拉下窗帘！
Pull out the houselights as soon as she finishes the chorus.
拉出家里的灯 她一唱完副歌。
Give her a chance. See how that song goes.
给她一个机会。 看看这首歌唱得怎么样。
The song is gone. Pull out the lights.
歌没了。 拉出灯。
- No, don't do it. - Who does she think she is?
- 不，不要这样做。 - 她以为她是谁？
Who does she think is running this theater? What does she mean by changing her number?
她认为谁在经营这个剧院？ 她换号码是什么意思？
The only reason I put her on was because the dog act got drunk.
我穿上她的唯一原因是 因为狗的行为喝醉了。
- He'll be all right in the morning. - Oh, she was your idea.
- 他早上会没事的。 - 哦，她是你的主意。
- And a very good idea too. - Now I know who got the dog act drunk.
- 也是一个非常好的主意。 - 现在我知道是谁让狗喝醉了。
Who, me? Why, I've never been in a saloon in my life.
谁，我？为什么，我从来没有 在我的生活中一直在沙龙。
And style enough to kill
和风格足以杀死
Her steady fella broke a dice game Down in Louisville
她稳定的家伙打破了一个 路易斯维尔的骰子游戏
Now look at that. Could you ask for anything more than that?
现在看看那个。你能问一下吗 除此之外？
Hmm? Just wait. She's wonderful, I think. Don't you think so?
唔？等一下。她很棒，我想。 你不这么认为吗？
- Don't do that! - Ha-ha-ha!
- 不要那样做！ - 哈哈哈！
Don't do that! Pull out the lights. Pull down that curtain.
不要那样做！拉出灯。 拉下那个窗帘。
She...
她...
Get your props together. You're on next.
把你的道具放在一起。 你在下一个。
Hey, boys, start limbering up. You follow the jugglers.
嘿，孩子们，开始放松吧。 你跟着杂耍者。
You get that curtain up. You can't ring down on a George M. Cohan song.
你把窗帘拉上。你不能 听一首 George M. Cohan 的歌。
A George M...? Oh, I see.
乔治M....？我懂了。
Oh, it's your song. You wrote it.
哦，那是你的歌。你写的。
You can tell that by the applause.
你可以从掌声中看出这一点。
Now, Mary, go out there and do an encore.
现在，玛丽， 去那里做一个安可。
- Do one more chorus, and really do it. - Oh, no. No, you don't.
- 再唱一首合唱，然后真的去做。 - 不好了。不，你没有。
Young lady, if you're gonna be trying out any junk like that...
年轻的女士，如果你愿意的话 尝试任何这样的垃圾......
...do it on a split-fee time, but you'll not be singing songs like that in my theater.
......在分费时间做，但你不会 在我的剧院里唱这样的歌。
Now you take a little tip from me: you start packing.
现在你从我这里得到一个小提示： 你开始打包。
If you've got any squawks, unload them on me. I'm the one that started all this.
如果您有任何尖叫声，请卸载它们 包在我身上。我是这一切的始作俑者。
Listen, squirt, any more interference on your part and you'll be blacklisted.
听，喷，再干扰 就您而言，您将被列入黑名单。
You won't even be able to get into a stage door of any theater...
你甚至无法得到 进入任何剧院的舞台门......
...and what's more, as for those songs of yours...
……更重要的是， 至于你的那些歌……
...they won't even be played on a hurdy-gurdy.
...他们甚至不会被播放 在手风琴上。
- Are you trying to threaten me? MARY: Oh!
- 你是想威胁我吗？ - 哦！
GEORGE: Mary! Mary! Don't pay any attention to him now.
玛丽！玛丽！不要付款 现在注意他。
Give me the key to your dressing room.
把钥匙给我 你的更衣室。
Drunk or sober, the dog act goes on in the next show.
醉酒或清醒， 狗的行为在下一个节目中继续。
And look here...
看这里...
Bring down the curtain!
拉下窗帘！
Cohan, you're fired.
科汉，你被解雇了。
You're canceled! You're washed up!
你被取消了！你被洗干净了！
You and your whole family!
你和你全家！
GEORGE: Oh, things were tough.
哦，事情很艰难。
Well, at least I was in New York.
好吧，至少我在纽约。
I had a trunkful of songs and play scripts...
我有一大堆歌曲 并播放脚本...
...and a heart full of confidence.
……还有一颗充满自信的心。
I'm glad I had it.
我很高兴我拥有它。
I'm sorry. I can't use this, Cohan.
对不起。我不能用这个，科汉。
Youth needs confidence.
青年需要自信。
I'd learned my job the hard way, all over the United States.
我以艰难的方式学会了我的工作， 遍布美国。
Guys who had never been past the corner cigar store...
从未过去的人 街角的雪茄店……
...were saying my stuff was no good.
……说我的东西不好。
A kid had to believe in himself to buck that.
一个孩子必须相信自己 反抗。
[SINGING] Who is the man who will spend Or will even lend?
谁是会花钱的人 或者甚至会借钱？
- Harrigan - That's me
- 哈里根 - 这就是我
Who is your friend when you find That you need a friend?
当你找到谁是你的朋友 你需要一个朋友吗？
- Harrigan - That's me
- 哈里根 - 这就是我
I'm just as proud of me name, you see As an emperor, czar, or a king could be
我为我的名字感到骄傲，你看 作为皇帝、沙皇或国王，可以
Who is the man helps a man Every time he can?
谁是男人帮助男人 每次他都可以？
- Harrigan - That's me
- 哈里根 - 这就是我
- H - A
- H - 一个
Double R-I
双 R-I
G-A-N spells Harrigan
G-A-N 拼写哈里根
Proud of all the Irish blood That's in me
为所有爱尔兰血统感到自豪 那在我里面
And never a man can say A word against me
从来没有一个人可以说 一句话反对我
- H - A
- H - 一个
Double R-I
双 R-I
G-A-N, you see Tlick
G-A-N，你看 滴答声
Is a name that a shame Never has been connected with
是一个耻辱的名字吗 从来没有联系过
Harrigan That's me
哈里根 这就是我
H-A
哈
Double R-I
双 R-I
G-A-N spells Harrigan
G-A-N 拼写哈里根
Proud of all the Irish blood That's in me
为所有爱尔兰血统感到自豪 那在我里面
Never a man can say A word against me
男人永远不能说 一句话反对我
H-A
哈
Double R-I
双 R-I
G-A-N, you see
G-A-N，你看
Is a name that a shame Never has been connected with
是一个耻辱的名字吗 从来没有联系过
Harrigan That's me
哈里根 这就是我
- Well, what do you think? - I didn't like it. It didn't appeal to me.
- 那么你觉得呢？ - 我不喜欢它。它没有吸引我。
What do you mean, you? I'm the senior partner around here.
你什么意思，你？ 我是这里的高级合伙人。
- I make the decisions. - Well, what did you think?
- 我做决定。 - 嗯，你怎么想的？
It didn't appeal to me, either.
它也没有吸引我。
Which proves, gentlemen, that you have no ear for music.
先生们，这证明了， 你没有听音乐的耳朵。
He's got no ear for music. I'm the senior partner.
他没有听音乐的耳朵。 我是高级合伙人。
I have a wonderful ear for music.
我的耳朵很听音乐。
But what about the libretto? It's a grand story, isn't it?
但是歌词呢？ 这是一个伟大的故事，不是吗？
- I laughed all the way through it. - That's my cue.
- 我一直在笑。 - 这是我的暗示。
If Harold laughs, then I know it isn't funny.
如果哈罗德笑了， 然后我知道这不好笑。
Have Mr. Cohan sing the rest of the score for you.
让科汉先生唱 剩下的分数给你。
Maybe you didn't like Harrigan because I haven't got a voice.
也许你不喜欢哈里根 因为我没有声音。
Oh, I think you have a lovely voice.
哦，我觉得你的声音很好听。
- Don't you think so, Mr. Dietz? - Yes, you have a very nice voice.
- 你不这么认为吗，迪茨先生？ - 是的，你的声音很好听。
In fact, if you'd like a job answering our phone...
事实上，如果你想要一份工作 接听我们的电话...
Are you or are you not going to produce my play?
你去还是不去 制作我的剧本？
If you think I'd put any of my wife's money into that trash, you're crazy.
如果你认为我会把我妻子的任何一个 把钱扔进那个垃圾箱，你疯了。
That's it, Mary. That's enough. They've had their chance.
就是这样，玛丽。够了。 他们有机会。
- Have you an appointment? - Yes. Sam Harris.
- 你有约会吗？ - 是的。山姆·哈里斯。
I want to see them about this melodrama I have.
我想见他们呢 关于我有的这部情节剧。
DIETZ: We have no time to listen to that junk.
我们没有时间 听那个垃圾。
You don't know it, boys, but your days are numbered.
你不知道，孩子们， 但你的日子屈指可数。
You're making room for the likes of me.
你在腾地方 对于我这样的人。
And someday, Mr. Senior Partner, you're gonna come to me and admit you were wrong.
总有一天，高级合伙人先生，你会 会来找我承认你错了。
In 20 years of show business, I never once admitted I was wrong.
从事演艺事业20年， 我从来没有承认我错了。
That's his department.
那是他的部门。
- And as for your wife's money... - Excuse me. I have an appointment.
- 至于你妻子的钱... - 打扰一下。我有一个预约。
- Who are you? - My name's Sam Harris.
- 你是谁？ - 我的名字是山姆哈里斯。
I have a melodrama here called Wildflower.
我有一部情节剧 这里叫野花。
Wildflower.
野花。
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10.
一二三四五， 六、七、八、九、十。
- Horses. - Oh, and Indians. Uh-oh.
- 马匹。 - 哦，还有印第安人。哦哦。
Don't let a couple of Gilberts like that get under your skin.
不要让几个吉尔伯特 像这样得到你的皮肤。
There's no sense in crying now.
现在哭也没有意义。
Buffalo is such a beautiful city.
布法罗是一座如此美丽的城市。
Is that what you're crying about?
这就是你哭的原因吗？
It's a beautiful city, but I hate to go back to it.
这是一座美丽的城市， 但我讨厌回到过去。
Don't worry. You won't have to. I'll show them yet.
不用担心。你不必。 我还要给他们看。
I'm gonna have my name up and down Broadway...
我会有我的名字 百老汇上下...
...until I'm as well known as Hood's Sarsaparilla. We'll whip them to a standstill.
直到我和胡德的菝葜一样出名。 我们会让他们停下来。
- Like Grant took Richmond. - I never really thought of leaving.
- 就像格兰特带走了里士满一样。 - 我从来没有真正想过离开。
We'll make this whole business sit up and holler for help.
我们会做这整个生意 坐起来大声呼救。
That's what we'll do. They'll all hear from us, every one of them.
这就是我们要做的。他们都会 听取我们的意见，他们每个人。
DIETZ: I'm the senior partner. I'll do the throwing out.
我是高级合伙人。 我会做扔掉的。
SAM: You don't have to throw me out. I know the way.
你不必扔 我出去。我知道路。
That's the last time I'll ever bring you a play.
那是最后一次 我会永远给你带来一出戏。
That's my department.
那是我的部门。
Now I will take it to Klaw and Erlanger. They don't always think of box office.
现在我会把它带给克劳和厄兰格。 他们并不总是想到票房。
Thanks.
谢谢。
- Too expensive. - Didn't even read the second act.
- 太贵了。 - 甚至没有读过第二幕。
Probably the biggest forest fire ever put on the stage.
可能是最大的森林火灾 曾经登上舞台。
I think he's a little upset.
我觉得他有点生气。
Five-thirty. We'd have done eight shows by this time in Buffalo.
五点半。我们会做八 此时在布法罗演出。
- The juggler just paid three weeks' back board. - Oh!
杂耍者刚刚付了钱 三周的背板。
Put him at the head so he doesn't have to reach.
把他放在头上 所以他不必伸手去拿。
Where shall I put the magician?
我应该把魔术师放在哪里？
Until he's paid, he sits at the foot of the table with the Cohans.
在他付钱之前，他坐在脚边 与 Cohans 的表。
Oh, starvation corner.
哦，饥饿的角落。
And put the goulash at the head of the table and keep everything...
把炖牛肉放在头上 桌子并保留一切...
...but the noodles and the maple syrup out of the reach of the Cohans.
...但是面条和枫糖浆 远离科汉家族。
Noodles and syrup are just enough to keep them alive.
面条和糖浆就够了 让他们活着。
Anybody who owes me two months' board bill, I just keep alive.
欠我两个月的人 董事会账单，我只是活着。
I don't have to wait on them.
我不必等他们。
MAN 1: Good evening, Madame. MAN 2: Good evening, Madame.
- 晚安，夫人。
Oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
- From now on, this is your seat. - Oh, thank you.
- 从现在开始，这是你的座位。 - 哦谢谢。
And you, master magician, you sit over there with the Cohans.
而你，魔法大师， 你和科汉一家坐在那里。
Heh. Madame, someday I hope you will give me the pleasure...
呵呵。夫人，我希望有一天 你会给我快乐...
...of sawing you in half.
……把你锯成两半。
- Ha-ha-ha! - I just heard today...
- 哈哈哈！ - 我今天才听说...
...that Hammerstein was bringing over the Scotch actor...
...汉默斯坦带来的 苏格兰演员...
...Harry Lauter, at 2500 bucks a week.
......哈利劳特， 每周2500美元。
Hammerstein's a great showman. A lot of people have never seen a Scotchman.
汉默斯坦是一个伟大的表演者。很多 的人从未见过苏格兰人。
- Take some goulash, Mrs. Cohan. NELLIE: Thank you.
- 来点炖牛肉吧，科汉太太。 - 谢谢。
Did you have that appointment with that man about your booking?
你有那个约会吗 和那个人谈你的预订？
Oh, yes, he's going to give work to the act any day now.
哦，是的，他要工作 立即行动。
What happened to that Boston offer you got?
发生了什么 对你得到的波士顿报价？
That was a mighty sweet proposition.
这是一个非常甜蜜的提议。
Four weeks guaranteed at $300 a week and top billing.
每周 300 美元保证四个星期 和顶级计费。
Well, we didn't take it. See, it just wasn't right.
好吧，我们没有接受。 看，只是不对劲。
MADAME: Any act that lays off as long as you have, any offer's all right.
任何下岗只要 你有，任何报价都可以。
WOMAN: Butter?
黄油？
We just thought we'd rest a few more weeks.
我们只是以为我们会 再休息几个星期。
Yes, you see, my brother's writing some new material for us...
是的，你看，我哥哥写的 给我们一些新材料...
...and, well, we're just not ready to open.
...而且，好吧，我们只是 还没准备好打开。
MAN 1: You're not fooling anybody.
你不是在愚弄任何人。
Everybody knows that you and Nellie and Josie can get work anytime, anyplace. Heh.
每个人都知道你和内莉还有 乔西可以随时随地工作。呵呵。
But nobody wants Georgie.
但没有人想要乔治。
MAN 2: Sure. He's made trouble in every theater this side of San Francisco.
当然。他在每一个方面都制造了麻烦 旧金山这边的剧院。
MAN 3: You can't lay off just because every manager has blackballed Georgie.
你不能因为每一个 经理把乔治拉黑了。
His family hasn't blackballed him.
他的家人没有黑他。
We may have to take hard knocks and make a lot of sacrifices...
我们可能不得不承受重击 并做出很多牺牲...
...but if they want our act, they'll have to take him too.
...但如果他们想要我们的行动， 他们也得带走他。
We're not breaking up our act or our family. And besides...
我们不会破坏我们的行为 或我们的家人。而且除了...
JERRY: All right, all right, let the blackballs fall where they may.
好吧好吧，让 黑球落在他们可能的地方。
GEORGE: Madame Bartholdi, champagne for everybody!
巴托尔迪夫人， 香槟给大家！
- If I had it, who would pay for it? - Dietz and Goff.
- 如果我有，谁来买单？ - 迪茨和戈夫。
- They're producing Little Johnny Jones. NELLIE: Oh, George, really?
- 他们正在制作小约翰尼琼斯。 - 哦，乔治，真的吗？
When Dietz heard the music, he said to heck with his wife's money, he's gonna use his own.
当迪茨听到音乐时，他说见鬼 用他妻子的钱，他会用自己的。
A second round of champagne on me, if you had any.
给我第二轮香槟， 如果你有的话。
Pass that goulash down to this end of the table.
把那个炖牛肉传下去 到桌子的这一端。
Oh, George.
哦，乔治。
Think of those billboards.
想想那些广告牌。
Book, music and lyrics, all by George M. Cohan.
书籍、音乐和歌词， 全部由乔治·M·科汉 (George M. Cohan) 撰写。
- Oh, Georgie, I... - Oh, now, take it easy, Josie.
- 哦，乔治，我... - 哦，现在，放轻松，乔西。
- There's enough water in the goulash now. - Heh-heh-heh.
- 现在炖牛肉里有足够的水了。 - 嘿嘿嘿。
Oh, uh, Dad, I'm gonna be tied up in rehearsal for the next few months.
哦，呃，爸爸，我要被绑起来了 在接下来的几个月里排练。
Why don't you and mom and Josie take whatever offers in the meantime to fill in.
你和妈妈和乔西为什么不带走 在此期间提供的任何内容都可以填写。
Well, I hate to see the act split up, George, but if you think so.
好吧，我讨厌看到表演分裂 起来，乔治，但如果你这么认为的话。
Oh, sure. You can play all that stuff around Chicago for Sullivan.
行，可以。你可以玩所有的东西 沙利文在芝加哥附近。
The money's good, and the jumps are short.
有钱就好 跳跃很短。
It's a good idea. You get tired resting too long.
这是个好主意。 休息太久会累。
But it won't be the same going back on the road without you, Georgie.
但回去就不一样了 在没有你的路上，乔治。
Why, we'll be like a carriage with only three wheels.
为什么，我们会像一辆马车 只有三个轮子。
But you will admit I was a bumpy wheel. You'll roll along a whole lot easier without me.
但你会承认我是一个颠簸的轮子。 没有我，你会轻松很多。
- Oh, no, Georgie. - Oh, but you will.
- 哦，不，乔治。 - 哦，但你会的。
Is there a part in your play for a bicycle rider?
你的戏里有戏吗 对于骑自行车的人？
I used to be known as "Venus on wheels."
我曾经是众所周知的 作为“车轮上的维纳斯”。
Mm-hm. I always knew you weren't a cook.
嗯嗯。我就知道 你不是厨师。
- How's everything going, George? - Not so good, kid. Not so good.
- 一切都好吗，乔治？ - 不太好，孩子。不太好。
I've been pounding the pavement so long, my socks have bunions.
我在人行道上砸了这么久， 我的袜子有拇囊炎。
- Say, Matt, would you put a head on that? MATT: You bet I will.
- 说，马特，你会注意吗？ - 你打赌我会的。
The villain says, "I'll tell the girl who you are unless you help me hold up this train.
恶棍说：“我会告诉那个女孩你是谁 除非你帮我撑起这列火车。
Think fast. It's due in 10 minutes."
快速思考。 10分钟后到期。”
You'll have the audience standing with excitement.
你会让观众站起来 兴奋地。
I know, I know. The hero helps him, gets shot in the leg...
我知道我知道。英雄帮助他， 腿中枪了……
...and the girl nurses him back to health.
...和女护士 他恢复健康。
No, no, no. He gets shot in the arm, Mr. Schwab, not the leg.
不不不。他手臂中弹， 施瓦布先生，不是腿。
- You know what happens next? - I won't be in the theater to find out.
- 你知道接下来会发生什么吗？ - 我不会在剧院里找到答案。
I will be down the street watching a musical comedy.
我会在街上 看音乐喜剧。
Before I put $10,000 into a show...
在我投入 10,000 美元参加演出之前...
...it must have songs, dances, and a lot of girls.
...它必须有歌曲，舞蹈， 和很多女孩。
Mmm! Women, women. Little rose petals.
嗯！女人，女人。 小玫瑰花瓣。
Now, the big scene is where the hero saves the girl from a burning forest fire.
现在，大场面是英雄救人的地方 森林大火中的女孩。
It won't be terribly expensive, Mr. Schwab. I know where I can get a cheap fire.
施瓦布先生，它不会很贵。 我知道哪里可以买到便宜的火。
SCHWAB: You don't need much of a fire, just enough to burn that manuscript.
你不需要太多的火，只要 足以烧掉那份手稿。
- Oh, here you are! I've been looking for you. SAM: What?
- 哦，你来了！我一直在找你。 - 什么？
We gotta go to Dietz and Goff and sign those papers.
我们得去找迪茨和戈夫 并签署这些文件。
- Papers? What papers? - What...? What papers?
- 论文？什么论文？ - 什么...？什么论文？
You don't want to talk about it in front of Schwab.
你不想谈论它 在施瓦布面前。
You haven't discussed our musical with Schwab?
你还没有讨论过我们的音乐剧 与施瓦布？
- Music? - We promised Dietz and Goff.
- 音乐？ - 我们答应了迪茨和戈夫。
I haven't said a word about a musical.
我没说一句话 关于音乐剧。
Good. Dietz said it's the best musical he's ever read.
好的。迪茨说这是 他读过的最好的音乐剧。
Even allowed Goff to agree with him.
甚至允许高夫同意他的看法。
When I told him about those 20 ponies and 20 showgirls all coming downstage...
当我告诉他那 20 匹小马 20 位歌舞女郎纷纷下台……
- Ponies and showgirls? - Just a minute.
- 小马和歌舞女郎？ - 请稍等。
- What are you talking about? - Waiter, waiter!
- 你在说什么？ - 服务员，服务员！
- Check for this table. - No, no, no. That's mine.
- 检查此表。 - 不不不。那是我的。
Oh, no, no... Well, we won't argue about it.
哦，不，不…… 好吧，我们不会为此争论。
- Glad to have met you, Mr. Schwab. - That's mine.
- 很高兴认识你，施瓦布先生。 - 那是我的。
- Come on, we can't keep Dietz waiting. - You are a fine guy.
- 来吧，我们不能让迪茨等着。 - 你是个好人。
You have girls up your sleeve.
你有女孩在你的袖子。
You have ponies and showgirls, and you don't tell me about it?
你有小马和歌舞女郎， 你不告诉我吗？
- What...? What's it about? - We gave our word to Dietz.
- 什么...？那是关于什么的？ - 我们向迪茨保证。
No time for details. It's about Todd Sloan in London.
没时间细说。 这是关于伦敦的托德斯隆的。
- The famous jockey. - Yeah. Come on, partner.
- 著名的骑师。 - 是的。来吧，伙伴。
Jockey? Jockey sounds swell. Just my luck to miss out on it.
骑师？骑师声音大。 错过它只是我的运气。
Mmm. Well, good luck, boys.
嗯。好吧，祝你好运，孩子们。
Oh, uh, you forgot your manuscript.
哦，呃，你忘记了你的手稿。
Before we sign with Dietz and Goff, I made some change in the lyric...
在我们与迪茨和戈夫签约之前， 我对歌词做了一些改动...
...of "Yankee Doodle." - "Yankee Doodle"?
- ..“洋基涂鸦”。 - “洋基涂鸦”？
- It was perfect the way it was. - Oh, you're gonna like this.
- 它是完美的方式。 - 哦，你会喜欢这个的。
- Gives the number added value. Watch... - May I...? May I listen a little?
- 赋予数字附加值。手表... - 我可以...？我可以听一点吗？
- Well, think we should? - I don't know.
- 那么，认为我们应该？ - 我不知道。
- If you promise to be quiet. - I promise. I promise.
- 如果你答应保持安静。 - 我保证。我保证。
All right. Come on. There's a piano in the private room.
好的。来吧。 私人房间里有一架钢琴。
"Yankee Doodle."
“洋基涂鸦。”
Uh-huh. "Yankee Doodle Candy."
嗯。 “洋基涂鸦糖果。”
Dandy. "Yankee Doodle Dandy."
花花公子。 “洋基涂鸦花花公子。”
SCHWAB: "Yankee Doodle Candy."
“洋基涂鸦糖果。”
[SINGING] I'm a Yankee Doodle Dandy
我是洋基涂鸦花花公子
Yankee Doodle Do or die
洋基涂鸦 做或死
A real live nephew Of my Uncle Sam
一个真正的外甥 我的山姆大叔
Born on the Fourth of July
出生于七月四日
I've got a Yankee Doodle sweetheart
我有一个洋基涂鸦甜心
She's my Yankee Doodle joy
她是我的洋基涂鸦快乐
Yankee Doodle came to London Just to ride the ponies
洋基涂鸦来到伦敦 只是为了骑小马
I am that Yankee Doodle boy
我就是那个洋基涂鸦男孩
I have heard enough.
我已经听够了。
I will never forgive you for trying to palm off a forest fire on me...
我永远不会原谅你的尝试 扑灭我的森林大火...
...when you had that musical all the time.
...当你有那个 一直是音乐剧。
Yes, but we gave our word to Dietz.
是的，但我们向迪茨保证了我们的承诺。
I can't understand it.
我无法理解。
Why is Dietz's wife's money better than my wife's money?
为什么是迪茨妻子的钱 比我老婆的钱好吗？
Why?
为什么？
Must you give it to Dietz and Goff?
你必须把它交给迪茨和戈夫吗？
- Must you give it? - Well, I don't know.
- 一定要给吗？ - 嗯，我不知道。
I like Dietz, but I'm not too fond of Goff.
我喜欢迪茨，但我不是 太喜欢高夫了。
I'm crazy about Goff, but I haven't got any use for Dietz.
我对戈夫很着迷， 但我对迪茨没有任何用处。
Gentlemen, you are in perfect agreement.
先生们， 你完全同意。
I will give you a check to bind the deal.
我会给你一张支票 绑定交易。
Here.
这里。
Thank you. What's your partner's name?
谢谢你。 你的伴侣叫什么名字？
I don't know.
我不知道。
SAM: What's my partner's name? Ha-ha-ha!
我的搭档叫什么名字？哈哈哈！
Well, don't toy with the kid at a time like this.
好吧，不要玩弄孩子 在这样的时候。
Tell him. George M. Cohan.
告诉他。乔治·M·科汉。
George M. Cohan. C-O-H-A-N.
乔治·M·科汉。 C-O-H-A-N。
And what is my junior partner's name?
我的初级合伙人叫什么名字？
Sam H. Harris. Shake.
山姆·H·哈里斯。摇。
- Hello. What should I write? - Uh, Cohan and Harris.
- 你好。我应该写什么？ - 呃，科汉和哈里斯。
Cohan.
科汉。
- Mm-hm. - And Harris.
- 嗯。 - 还有哈里斯。
[SINGING] I'm the kid that's all the candy I'm a Yankee Doodle Dandy
我是所有的糖果的孩子 我是洋基涂鸦花花公子
I'm glad I am
我很高兴我是
CHORUS: So's Uncle Sam
山姆大叔也是
I'm a real-life Yankee Doodle Made my name on fame and boodle
我是现实生活中的洋基涂鸦 名声大噪
Just as Mr. Doodle did By riding on a pony
就像涂鸦先生所做的那样 骑着小马
I love to listen to the Dixie strain I long to see the girl I left behind me
我喜欢听迪克西应变 我渴望见到我留下的那个女孩
That ain't a josh She's a Yankee, by gosh
那不是乔希 她是个洋基人，天哪
CHORUS: O say can you see
O说你能看到吗
Anything about a Yankee That's awful neat
关于洋基队的任何事情 太整洁了
CHORUS: Little Johnny Jones A jockey from the U.S.A.
小约翰尼琼斯 来自美国的骑师
Will ride the pony, Yankee Doodle English derby day
会骑小马，洋基涂鸦 英国德比日
CHORUS: Jones has broken records Every track at every meet
琼斯打破了记录 每次见面的每首歌
So Yankee Doodle's gonna be The boy they have to beat
所以洋基涂鸦会 他们必须打败的男孩
CHORUS: Sergeant of the British Isles Who followed his career
不列颠群岛中士 谁追随他的职业生涯
Have offered Johnny anything To keep him over here
向约翰尼提供了任何东西 把他留在这里
But all the money in the Bank of England Couldn't pay
但是英格兰银行里的所有钱 无法支付
Enough to keep young Johnny Jones Away from old Broadway
足以留住年轻的约翰尼琼斯 远离老百老汇
CHORUS: If you want to take a trip The surest of sure things
如果你想去旅行 确定的事情中最确定的
Have your houses mortgaged Hock your watches, pawn your rings
抵押你的房子 打你的手表，典当你的戒指
CHORUS: And put it all on Yankee Doodle Johnny Jones is up
把它全部放在洋基涂鸦上 约翰尼琼斯起来了
I'm gonna give America The English derby cup
我要给美国 英格兰德比杯
CHORUS: He's gonna give America
他会给 美国 英格兰德比杯
I'm a Yankee Doodle Dandy
我是洋基涂鸦花花公子
Yankee Doodle Do or die
洋基涂鸦 做或死
A real live nephew Of my Uncle Sam
一个真正的外甥 我的山姆大叔
Born on the Fourth of July
出生于七月四日
I've got a Yankee Doodle sweetheart
我有一个洋基涂鸦甜心
She's my Yankee Doodle joy
她是我的洋基涂鸦快乐
Yankee Doodle came to London Just to ride the ponies
洋基涂鸦来到伦敦 只是为了骑小马
I am that Yankee Doodle boy
我就是那个洋基涂鸦男孩
CHORUS: He's a Yankee Doodle Dandy
他是洋基涂鸦花花公子
A Yankee Doodle Do or die
洋基涂鸦 做或死
A real live nephew of his Uncle Sam
他的山姆大叔的一个活生生的侄子
Born on the Fourth of July
出生于七月四日
He's got a Yankee Doodle sweetheart
他有一个洋基涂鸦甜心
She's his Yankee Doodle joy
她是他的洋基涂鸦欢乐
Yankee Doodle came to London Just to ride the ponies
洋基涂鸦来到伦敦 只是为了骑小马
He is a Yankee Doodle boy
他是洋基涂鸦男孩
Yankee Doodle came to London Just to ride the ponies
洋基涂鸦来到伦敦 只是为了骑小马
He is a Yankee Doodle boy
他是洋基涂鸦男孩
Good luck, Johnny Success to you
祝你好运，约翰尼 给你成功
All the best of the best to you
祝你万事如意
We'll make our bets And leave the rest to you
我们会下注 剩下的交给你
Because you've got What it takes to win
因为你有 获胜需要什么
There they are, going to the post All in good condition
他们在那里，去邮局 一切都很好
That's Yankee Doodle on the end A wonderful position
最后是洋基涂鸦 一个美妙的位置
Look at him rear, he's broken line He's simply wild to run
看他后面，他断线了 他简直是狂奔
Now they're back in line again There's the starting gun
现在他们又重新排队了 有发令枪
CHORUS: They're off Come on, Yankee Doodle
他们走了 来吧，洋基涂鸦
We have bet the whole caboodle on you Run, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up
我们已经把整堆赌注都押在了你身上 跑，快，快，快，快
Yankee takes the lead
洋基队领先
Break away there Show them how to earn their hay there
离开那里 向他们展示如何在那里赚取干草
How to run, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up Show a little speed
怎么跑，快点，快点，快点 显示一点速度
At the quarter, he's gaining At the turn now, he's reining his horse
在本季度，他正在获得 现在在转弯时，他正在勒马
Go, go, go, don't hold him back Let him go
走，走，走，别拦着他 让他走
At the half mark, he's cruising But seems to be losing his lead
在半分时，他正在巡航 但似乎正在失去领先优势
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up You simply have to win
快点快点快点 你只需要赢
He'll never win, he'll never win The other nags are closing in
他永远不会赢，他永远不会赢 其他的老马正在接近
- He's gone to third from second place - Looks like he's thrown the race
- 他从第二名跌至第三名 - 看起来他把比赛扔了
They've got him in a pocket He can't get in the clear
他们把他放在口袋里 他不能清楚
They're in the stretch, here they come He's falling to the rear
他们处于紧张状态，他们来了 他倒在后面
He's lost the race, but it's a frame
他输了比赛，但这是一个框架
We'll find the blighter who's to blame And clear the name of Little Johnny Jones
我们会找到应该受到责备的暴徒 并清除小约翰尼琼斯的名字
CROWD: Aw!
啊！
Well, that's it, ladies and gentlemen, it's all over.
嗯，就是这样，女士们和 先生们，一切都结束了。
Yankee Doodle let them down.
洋基涂鸦让他们失望了。
So they'll either pasture him in clover...
所以他们要么放牧 他在三叶草...
...or have him hauling rubbish in London Town.
...或者让他拖 伦敦城的垃圾。
CHORUS: Good-bye, Johnny
再见，强尼
We're through with you
我们和你一起结束了
We'll have nothing to do with you
我们与你无关
You've been dishonest.
你一直不诚实。
BOTH: And we find that you'll be suspended for throwing the race.
我们发现你会 因投掷比赛而被停赛。
I'm a Yankee Doodle Dandy.
我是洋基涂鸦花花公子。
Yankee Doodle, do or die.
洋基涂鸦，做或死。
Yankee Doodle came to London.
洋基涂鸦来到伦敦。
Just to ride the ponies.
只是为了骑小马。
I am that Yankee Doodle boy.
我就是那个洋基涂鸦男孩。
CHORUS: For he was that Yankee Doodle
因为他就是那个洋基涂鸦
Boy
男生
Women, women. Little rose petals.
女人，女人。小玫瑰花瓣。
Wonderful. You've got them eating right out of your hand.
精彩的。你让他们吃 就在你的手中。
- My congratulations. - Thanks, Sam.
- 我的祝贺。 - 谢谢，山姆。
As long as those critics don't eat off my leg.
只要那些批评者 不要吃掉我的腿。
Don't worry about the critics. You got a smash hit. It's in the air.
不要担心批评者。 你大获全胜。它在空中。
You can't stop anything that's in the air.
你无法阻止任何事情 那是在空中。
ALL [SINGING]: All aboard
全部登机
We'll soon be sailing for
我们很快就会航行
The city of old New York
旧纽约市
Broadway nights A million dancing lights
百老汇之夜 一百万盏舞灯
Thrilling sights everywhere you walk
到处都是令人兴奋的景点
London Town We're bidding you adieu
伦敦镇 我们向你告别
Gee, we hate to say good-bye to you
哎呀，我们讨厌跟你说再见
All aboard
全部登机
Good-bye to London Town
再见伦敦城
Hello to old Broadway
你好老百老汇
All right, on the boat.
好吧，在船上。
Now, remember, Jones, watch for the skyrocket.
现在，记住，琼斯， 注意暴涨。
If it goes off, you'll know that I've obtained certain papers from Ansty's cabin...
如果它熄灭，你就会知道我已经 从安斯蒂的小屋里拿到了一些文件……
...that'll prove you innocent of throwing the English derby.
...这将证明你是无辜的 投掷英式德比。
It'll mean complete vindication.
这将意味着完全的平反。
So stick here on the pier and watch for the skyrocket.
所以坚持在码头上 并注意飙升。
Thanks, pal. I'll be watching.
谢谢，伙计。我会看的。
Good-bye, Johnny. And don't worry, we still believe in you.
再见，约翰尼。别担心， 我们仍然相信你。
Thanks, kid. That'll help a lot.
谢谢，孩子。这会有很大帮助。
- Good-bye. - Bye.
- 再见。
[SINGING] Give my regards
转达我的问候
To Broadway
去百老汇
Remember me to Herald Square
记得我到先驱广场
Tell all the gang At 42nd Street
告诉所有的帮派 在第 42 街
That I will soon be there
我很快就会到那里
Whisper of how I am yearning
耳语我多么向往
To mingle with that old-time throng
与那昔日的人群混在一起
Give my regards
转达我的问候
To old Broadway And say that I'll be there ere long
去老百老汇 说我很快就会在那里
CHORUS: We'll give your regards to Broadway
我们将向您致意百老汇
Remember you to Herald Square
记得你到先驱广场
We'll tell all the gang At 42nd Street
我们会告诉所有的帮派 在第 42 街
That you will soon be there
你很快就会到那里
We'll whisper of how you're yearning
我们会耳语你的渴望
To mingle with the old-time throng
与旧时代的人群混在一起
We'll give your regards
我们会向您致意
To old Broadway
去老百老汇
And say that you'll be there ere long
并说你很快就会在那里
We'll whisper of how you're yearning
我们会耳语你的渴望
To mingle with the old-time throng
与旧时代的人群混在一起
We'll give your regards
我们会向您致意
To old Broadway
去老百老汇
And say that you'll be there ere long
并说你很快就会在那里
Ha-ha!
哈哈！
We'll whisper of how you're yearning
我们会耳语你的渴望
To mingle with the old-time throng
与旧时代的人群混在一起
We'll give your regards To old Broadway
我们会向您致意 去老百老汇
And say that you'll be there ere long
并说你很快就会在那里
That was your department.
那是你的部门。
Is it the robin that heralds the first breath of spring?
是知更鸟 春天的第一缕气息？
How can you think of robins in the spring when we're freezing to death in Illinois?
你怎么能想到春天的知更鸟 当我们在伊利诺伊州被冻死的时候？
MAN: Hey, Jerry, did you see the way they're billing you in Waukegan?
嘿，杰瑞，你看到路了吗 他们在沃基根向你收费吗？
Come here. Look at that. Funny, isn't it?
过来。看那个。 有趣，不是吗？
"Jerry, Nellie, and Josie Cohan...
“杰瑞、内莉和乔西·科汉……
...the family of George M. Cohan, the new Broadway sensation."
...乔治·M·科汉 (George M. Cohan) 的家人， 百老汇的新感觉。”
Hey, the kid's doing all right, isn't he?
嘿，孩子在做 好吧，不是吗？
JERRY: Look at that.
看那个。
Well, that's true. He is the biggest thing on Broadway.
嗯，这是真的。 他是百老汇最大的人物。
Yeah, I know, but it ain't right. We'll build our own reputation.
是的，我知道，但这是不对的。 我们将建立自己的声誉。
We'll be billed as we should be: The Three Cohans.
我们将按应有的方式收费： 三个科汉。
All right, no need to get excited.
好吧，不用激动。
Don't think I'm jealous of Georgie's success...
不要以为我嫉妒 乔治的成功...
...even though I am a better actor.
...即使我是一个更好的演员。
Of course you're not jealous. Everybody knows that.
你当然不嫉妒。 每个人都知道这一点。
NELLIE: Oh, there'll be no stopping George.
哦，不会阻止乔治的。
All he needs is a little more experience, and he'll be a genius.
他所需要的只是多一点经验， 他会是个天才。
He mustn't know I'm better. It might interfere with him becoming a genius.
他一定不知道我更好。它可能 妨碍他成为天才。
Still, it does look a little funny: George being the toast of Broadway...
不过，它看起来确实有点滑稽： 乔治成为百老汇的敬酒...
...and you folks gathering a few crumbs in the tank towns.
……你们聚在一起 坦克城镇的一些面包屑。
- Is either of you fellas Jerry Cohan? JERRY: I am.
- 你们两个是 Jerry Cohan 吗？ - 我是。
It's from George.
是乔治寄来的。
"Impossible to find three clever actors named Cohan...
“不可能找到三个 聪明的演员叫科汉...
...for my new show anywhere in New York.
...我的新节目 在纽约的任何地方。
Return immediately for rehearsals."
马上回来排练。”
- What'd I tell you? - The four of us back together again...
- 我跟你说了什么？ - 我们四个又聚在一起了……
...and on Broadway!
...在百老汇！
MEN [SINGING]: Oh, you wonderful girl
哦，你这个了不起的女孩
What a wonderful girl you are
你是个多么棒的女孩
You made the world appear to me
你让世界向我显现
Near to me, dear to me
靠近我，我亲爱的
WOMEN: Blue skies, gray skies
蓝蓝的天空，灰蒙蒙的天空
Main Street or Broadway skies
大街或百老汇的天空
ALL: Under December or May skies
在十二月或五月的天空下
I'll be true to you
我会对你真诚
Everybody's going to the barber's ball
每个人都去 去理发师的舞会
There ain't a-gonna be any sleep at all
不会有 睡不着觉
Until the stars are gone Until the break of dawn
直到星星消失 直到黎明破晓
We're going to dance At the barber's ball
我们要跳舞 在理发师的舞会上
Even in the kitchen, you sound like a tetrazzini.
即使在厨房里， 你听起来像个四人组。
Heh. In Buffalo, they say I have a nice little voice.
呵呵。在布法罗，他们说 我有一个很好的小声音。
Yeah. A lot they know in Buffalo. In Buffalo they thought I was an old man.
是的。他们在布法罗知道很多。 在布法罗，他们认为我是个老人。
Well, how do you like your part so far?
嗯，你喜欢怎样 到目前为止你的部分？
Oh, I like it. I like it because it's small.
哦，我喜欢它。 我喜欢它，因为它很小。
I'd be afraid to try anything bigger.
我会害怕尝试更大的东西。
You've got something on the leading lady. You got the best song.
你对女主角有一些了解。 你得到了最好的歌曲。
Here it is. It's finished. Come on.
这里是。都结束了。来吧。
- What about the lyrics? - Gonna give it to you now.
- 歌词呢？ - 现在就给你。
Sit down and give me a pickup.
坐下来给我提车。
My mother's name was Mary.
我母亲的名字是玛丽。
She was so good and true.
她是如此优秀和真实。
Because her name was Mary...
因为她的名字叫玛丽……
...she called me Mary too.
……她也叫我玛丽。
She wasn't gay or airy...
她不是同性恋，也不是空灵……
...but plain as she could be.
......但她可以很简单。
I'd hate to meet a Mary...
我不想见到玛丽...
...who called herself Marie.
...自称玛丽的人。
For it is Mary...
因为是玛丽...
...Mary...
...玛丽...
...plain as any name can be.
......就像任何名字一样简单。
But with propriety...
但是有礼貌...
...society...
...社会...
...will say, "Hm-hm. Marie."
......会说，“嗯，嗯。玛丽。”
But it was Mary...
但那是玛丽……
...Mary...
...玛丽...
...long before the fashions came.
...早在时尚到来之前。
And there is something there...
那里有东西……
...that sounds so square...
……听起来很方正……
...it's a grand old name.
...这是一个伟大的旧名字。
[SINGING] For it is Mary
因为是玛丽
Mary
玛丽
Plain as any name can be
像任何名字一样简单
BOTH: But with propriety
但有礼貌
Society will say, "Marie"
社会会说，“玛丽”
But it was Mary
但那是玛丽
Mary
玛丽
Long before the fashions came
早在时尚到来之前
And there is something there
那里有东西
That sounds so square
听起来很方正
It's a grand old name
这是一个伟大的老名字
Mm-hm. Yeah.
嗯嗯。是的。
Gee, I never cared much for my name before. It was kind of common.
哎呀，我从来不关心我的 之前的名字。这很常见。
Gee, there are millions of Marys around, but now...
哎呀，有几百万 玛丽斯在身边，但现在...
But I didn't write it for the millions of Marys.
但是我没写 为数以百万计的玛丽。
I wrote it for one particular, very special Mary.
我写它是为了一个特定的， 非常特别的玛丽。
Gee, it's a wonderful feeling having your name written to music.
哎呀，有一种美妙的感觉 你的名字写在音乐上。
- And not bad music, either, huh? - Nope, it isn't.
- 而且音乐也不错，是吧？ - 不，不是。
But how will everybody know that I'm the Mary?
但是大家怎么会知道 我是玛丽？
I want to make sure that everybody knows it was written for me.
我想确保每个人都知道 它是为我写的。
They'll know, all right.
他们会知道的，好吧。
When they look at you singing that song and then look at me looking at you...
当他们看着你唱那首歌 然后看着我看着你……
- ...they'll know. - Oh, George.
- ...他们会知道的。 - 哦，乔治。
Take that up an octave.
把它提高一个八度。
- George. - Better.
- 乔治。 - 更好的。
Excuse me for butting in. I've been looking all over town for you.
原谅我插嘴。 我一直在全城找你。
Strange that I should find you here. Hello, Mary.
奇怪我会在这里找到你。 你好，玛丽。
Mr. Harris, George has just written a new song for me to sing in his show.
哈里斯先生，乔治刚刚写信 我要在他的节目中唱一首新歌。
- Think I can do it? - Of course. You've got a nice little voice.
- 认为我能做到吗？ - 当然。你有一个很好听的小声音。
That is not a little voice, and you need an ear trumpet.
那不是一个小声音， 你需要一个喇叭。
Come on, we've gotta get off to the Lyceum. We've got to see Fay Templeton.
来吧，我们得去Lyceum了。 我们得见费伊·坦普尔顿。
- What does she want to see us about? - She doesn't. We want to see her.
- 她想见我们做什么？ - 她没有。我们想见她。
You need a leading lady. You've got your ingenue.
你需要一个女主角。 你有你的天真。
- George. - Hmm, Fay Templeton. That's not bad.
- 乔治。 - 嗯，Fay Templeton。这还不错。
She can do four years for us.
她可以为我们做四年。
- Think she'll take it? - I don't know.
- 认为她会接受？ - 我不知道。
- At least you can get her autograph. GEORGE: Or for her to get mine.
- 至少你可以得到她的签名。 - 或者让她得到我的。
MARY: Bring her back to supper after the show.
带她回去 演出结束后的晚餐。
I will if she's still speaking to us.
如果她还在和我们说话，我会的。
WOMAN: Would you like to buy it? Thank you.
你想买吗？谢谢你。
SAM: There's one thing in our favor. Erlanger's on our side.
有一件事对我们有利。 厄兰格站在我们这边。
- He's got influence with Miss Templeton. - You talk to him, and I'll tackle Templeton.
- 他对坦普尔顿小姐有影响。 - 你跟他说话，我会对付坦普尔顿。
You don't tackle a star like Miss Templeton.
你不对付明星 像坦普尔顿小姐。
- You approach her and very tactfully too. - Well, if it's tact that does it, it's done.
- 你接近她，也非常委婉。 - 好吧，如果它是圆滑的，它就完成了。
If you get me in to see Miss Templeton, I'll get you two passes to my next show.
如果你让我去见坦普尔顿小姐， 我会给你两张通行证参加我的下一场演出。
Dan, look. Dietz. Looks naked without Goff.
丹，看。迪茨。 没有 Goff 看起来很赤裸。
Heh. Yeah. Where's Miss Templeton's dressing room?
呵呵。是的。小姐在哪里 坦普尔顿的更衣室”？
MAN: Upstairs. - I tell you what I'm going to do.
- 楼上。 - 我告诉你我要做什么。
I'm gonna see to it that Miss Templeton gets your flowers.
我会照顾好小姐 坦普尔顿得到你的花。
My respects to Mrs. Dietz.
我向迪茨夫人致敬。
[SLURRING] Now, that was a very sweet gesture.
现在，这是一个非常甜蜜的姿态。
But you've got to remember, Fay, we're having a tough time...
但你必须记住，Fay， 我们过得很艰难...
...lining up a vehicle for you.
...为您安排车辆。
Now, you should listen to this man.
现在，你应该听这个人的。
- He's just written a big hit. - One hit.
- 他刚刚写了一个大热门。 - 一击。
He may be a flash in the pan for all we know.
他可能是昙花一现 据我们所知。
And I heard about Little Johnny Jones.
我听说 小约翰尼琼斯。
And I read the critics... Pfft.
我读了评论家...... Pfft。
-- of all the loud, vulgar flag-waving.
...在所有响亮的声音中， 粗俗的挥舞旗帜。
Well, it was a wow. I haven't laughed so much in years.
嗯，这是一个哇。 好多年没这么笑过了。
The fellow's got the golden touch.
这家伙有金手指。
Maybe so, but not for me, Mr. Erlanger.
也许是这样，但不是 对我来说，厄兰格先生。
What I want is a quiet, dignified musical play.
我要的是安静， 庄严的音乐剧。
I want to perform in a theater, not a boiler factory.
我想在剧院演出， 不是锅炉厂。
ERLANGER: Come in.
进来。
- Hello, Harris. How are you, Cohan? - Hello, Abe.
- 你好，哈里斯。你好吗，科汉？ - 你好，安倍。
Everything's all right. You'll see.
一切都好。你会看到的。
Oh, uh, Fay, uh, may I present Mr. Harris.
哦，呃，费， 呃，我可以介绍一下哈里斯先生吗？
- How do you do? - And, uh, Fay, this is Mr. Cohan.
- 你好吗？ - 还有，呃，费伊，这是科汉先生。
- George M. Cohan. - How do you do?
- 乔治 M. 科汉。 - 你好吗？
We were just talking about you, George. Miss Templeton's never seen your work.
我们只是在谈论你，乔治。 坦普尔顿小姐从未看过你的作品。
Hmm. Been sick or in Europe?
唔。生病了还是在欧洲？
No. I've been right here on this stage for two years.
不，我一直在这里 这个阶段两年。
Oh, buried.
哦，被埋了。
Oh, uh, don't misunderstand me, Miss Templeton. I, uh...
哦，呃，不要误会我， 坦普尔顿小姐。我，呃...
Well, I've never been at a loss for words before...
嗯，我从来没有 之前不知所措……
...but right now standing here in your presence, why, I hardly...
……但现在站在这里 在你面前，为什么，我几乎……
Well, I'd prefer to have these flowers speak for me.
嗯，我宁愿有 这些花代表我。
- Why, Mr. Cohan, how sweet of you. - Oh, it was nothing at all.
- 为什么，科汉先生，你真可爱。 - 哦，什么都没有。
Excuse me for breaking in on you like this, Miss Templeton...
原谅我闯入你 像这样，坦普尔顿小姐……
...but I would like to present my own flowers my own way.
...但我想介绍 我自己的花我自己的方式。
- But, Mr. Cohan, I thought... Is he? - Drunk.
- 但是，科汉先生，我想……是他吗？ - 喝醉了。
May I have the honor of supping with you at Rex's tonight after the show...
愿我有幸与我共进晚餐 你今晚在雷克斯演出结束后...
...and drinking champagne out of your...
...喝香槟 从你的...
- Pardon me. --slipper? SAM: Excuse me, Mr. Dietz.
- 原谅我....拖鞋？ - 对不起，迪茨先生。
Haven't you forgotten that your junior partner, Goff, does all the drinking?
你有没有忘记你的小辈 搭档，高夫，喝酒了吗？
Yes, but on special occasions, I take over...
是的，但在特殊场合， 我接手...
May I put these in water for you?
我可以帮你把这些放进水里吗？
- Well, really, I... ERLANGER: I never saw Dietz drunk before.
- 嗯，真的，我... - 我以前从没见过迪茨喝醉了。
Heh-heh. Well, uh, shall we get down to business?
呵呵。嗯，我们要不要 谈正事？
If you like, Abe.
如果你喜欢，安倍。
Well, George, how would you like to do a play...
那么，乔治， 你想怎么演戏...
...with one of the biggest stars in America?
...与最大的明星之一 在美国？
- What do you think I've been doing? - Heh. Yes.
- 你认为我一直在做什么？ - 嘿。是的。
You see what I mean, Fay? Heh-heh. Isn't he a card?
你明白我的意思吗，费？ 呵呵。他不是卡吗？
Positively a riot.
肯定是暴动。
Yes, well, George, what's your new story like?
是的，乔治， 你的新故事是什么样的？
That is, I mean, can you write a play without a flag?
也就是说，我的意思是， 你能写出没有旗子的剧本吗？
Miss Templeton, I can write a play without anything except a pencil.
坦普尔顿小姐，我可以写一出戏 除了铅笔，什么都没有。
- Laugh. Now, look... - There's really no use discussing anything.
- 笑。现在，看... - 讨论任何事情真的没有用。
I would never please the sort of people who revel in your antics and fireworks.
我永远不会取悦那种人 谁陶醉于你的滑稽动作和烟火。
Oh, you're just being modest, Miss Templeton.
哦，你只是谦虚， 坦普尔顿小姐。
If you'd let yourself go, you'd be just as noisy and entertaining as the rest of us.
如果你放手，你会像 像我们其他人一样嘈杂和有趣。
You might even have fun yourself.
你甚至可以自己玩得开心。
Abe, isn't it about time for the curtain to go up?
安倍，是不是时候到了 窗帘升起？
Look, if you haven't got time now, maybe a few minutes after the show.
看，如果你现在没有时间， 可能在演出后几分钟。
I'm sorry. After the show I'm going home to New Rochelle.
对不起。演出结束后 我要回新罗谢尔的家。
It's only 45 minutes from here...
距离这里只有45分钟...
...but it's like a thousand miles from all the noisy, neurotic people...
...但它就像一千英里 来自所有吵闹、神经质的人……
...one has to associate with in our profession.
...一个人必须与 在我们的职业中。
GEORGE: Now, Miss Templeton, you can't...
现在，坦普尔顿小姐，你不能……
ERLANGER: Fay, I warned you. - That tact of yours. That wonderful tact.
- 费伊，我警告过你。 - 你的机智。那美妙的机智。
What are you thinking about?
你在想什么？
Well, have you thought it over, Fay?
那么，你考虑好了吗，费？
I'm not interested in Mr. Cohan or his plays.
我对科汉先生不感兴趣 或他的戏剧。
Now you're making a great mistake, Fay.
现在你正在制作一个 大错特错，费。
He's the most original thing that ever hit Broadway. You know why?
他是最原始的东西 曾经打过百老汇。你知道为什么？
Because he's the whole darn country squeezed into one pair of pants.
因为他是整个该死的国家 挤进一条裤子里。
His writing, his song, why, even his walk and his talk...
他的作品，他的歌，为什么， 甚至他的走路和说话...
...they all touch something way down here in people.
...他们都触摸到了一些东西 人在这里。
Now, don't ask me why it is, but it happens every time the curtain goes up.
现在，不要问我为什么会这样，但它 每次大幕拉开时都会发生。
It's pure magic.
这是纯粹的魔法。
I'm bored by magic. I know his formula.
我对魔法感到厌烦。 我知道他的公式。
A fresh, young sprout gets rich between 8:30 and 11 p.m.
一个新鲜的嫩芽变得富有 晚上 8 点 30 分到 11 点之间
Yes, that's just it, Fay.
是的，就是这样，Fay。
George M. Cohan has invented the success story.
George M. Cohan 发明了 成功的故事。
And every American loves it because it happens to be his own private dream.
每个美国人都喜欢它，因为 这恰好是他自己的私人梦想。
He's found the mainspring in the antique clock.
他找到了主发条 在古董钟里。
Ambition, pride, patriotism.
野心、自豪、爱国。
That's why they call him the Yankee Doodle boy.
这就是为什么他们叫他 洋基涂鸦男孩。
Now, if you'll take a tip from me, Fay, you'll do just what I'm doing.
现在，如果你愿意接受我的小费，Fay， 你会做我正在做的事。
You'll hitch your wagon to his star right now.
你会搭上你的马车 现在去他的明星。
Abe, I've got to change for the second act.
安倍，我必须改变 对于第二幕。
Now, Fay, don't make up your mind too quickly.
现在，Fay，不要化妆 你的头脑太快了。
Take a little time. Think it over.
花一点时间。想一想。
Who's locked my door?
谁锁了我的门？
SAM: Who is it? FAY: What's going on here?
- 是谁？ - 这里发生了什么？
He'll be through in a minute.
他会在一分钟内完成。
Excuse me. I beg your pardon. I didn't realize who you were. Come in.
打扰一下。请再说一遍。 我没有意识到你是谁。进来。
- May I? - Why, of course.
- 我可以？ - 为什么，当然。
What does this mean?
这是什么意思？
Would you mind telling me why you're still here?
你介意告诉我吗 为什么你还在这里？
Well, here it is, ready and dedicated to you.
嗯，就是这样， 准备好并献给您。
- What? - Well, uh, when you made that exit speech...
- 什么？ - 嗯，呃，当你发表演讲时...
...you said you lived only 45 minutes away.
……你说你活着 仅 45 分钟路程。
That struck me as being a perfect title for a show and for a song.
这让我觉得完美 节目和歌曲的标题。
During the first act, you've written this new song?
在第一幕中， 你写过这首新歌吗？
Strange surrounding. It took me longer.
奇怪的周围。 我花了更长的时间。
He's worked so hard. The least you could do is hear it.
他已经很努力了。 你至少能听到它。
- Yeah, it'll only take a minute, won't it? - Depends on the encores. Heh.
- 是的，只需要一分钟，不是吗？ - 取决于安可。呵呵。
Well, you certainly are persistent. All right, go ahead.
好吧，你当然是坚持不懈的。 好吧，继续。
- Mind if I change? SAM: Oh, thank you.
- 介意我改变吗？ - 哦谢谢。
That's wonderful of you. Thank you very, very much. Go ahead, George. Play it.
你真棒。非常感谢， 非常。继续，乔治。玩。
[SINGING] Only 45 minutes from Broadway
距百老汇仅 45 分钟路程
Think of the changes it brings
想想它带来的改变
For the short time it takes What a difference it makes
在短时间内 它有什么不同
In the ways of the people and things
在人和事的方式上
Oh, what a fine bunch of Reubens
哦，多么棒的一群鲁本斯
Oh, what a jay atmosphere
哦，多么欢乐的气氛
They have whiskers like hay And imagine Broadway
他们有像干草一样的胡须 想象一下百老汇
Only 45 minutes from here
距离这里仅 45 分钟
Only 45 minutes
仅45分钟
That's good. It's rather different.
那挺好的。这是相当不同的。
- You liked it, Miss Templeton? FAY: Ah!
- 你喜欢吗，坦普尔顿小姐？ - 啊！
Excuse me. That's only a chorus number.
打扰一下。 那只是一个合唱号码。
He's got one number called "Mary" that's perfect for you.
他有一个号码叫“玛丽” 这对你来说是完美的。
- She doesn't sing that. - She is gonna sing it.
- 她不唱那个。 - 她会唱歌。
- No, no, no. - Shut up.
- 不不不。 - 住口。
It's the best thing he's ever done.
这是他做过的最好的事情。
"Mary," hmm?
“玛丽，”嗯？
This looks very interesting.
这看起来很有趣。
GEORGE: It's only a so-so number.
这只是一个马马虎虎的数字。
If it's as good as "45 Minutes from Broadway"...
如果它和“45分钟”一样好 来自百老汇”...
- Well, it isn't, and besides, you... - What do you want to do, spoil everything?
- 嗯，不是，而且，你…… - 你想做什么，破坏一切？
- I can't let her have that. - What difference does it make?
- 我不能让她拥有那个。 - 它有什么不同？
- She's gonna sing it. She will. - But she can't sing it.
- 她会唱歌。她会。 - 但她不会唱。
With Abe's money and your brains, we'll be able to make a million.
用安倍的钱和你的大脑， 我们将能够赚到一百万。
SAM: Shh!
嘘！
[SINGING] For it is Mary
因为是玛丽
Mary
玛丽
Society will say
社会会说
"Marie"
“玛丽”
But it was Mary
但那是玛丽
Mary
玛丽
Long before the fashions came
早在时尚到来之前
Come in.
进来。
Oh! A little early for Christmas, isn't it?
哦！有点早了 圣诞节，不是吗？
Well, I was just passing the flowers, and they threw in the candy.
好吧，我只是路过鲜花， 他们把糖果扔了进去。
George, I'm sure our song will live forever.
乔治，我相信我们的 歌将永存。
I've been playing it ever since you left, and the neighbors haven't complained once.
自从你离开后我就一直在玩 邻居们也没有抱怨过一次。
What happened with Fay Templeton?
费伊邓普顿怎么了？
Oh, she's dying to play the part. But I haven't made up my mind yet.
哦，她渴望扮演这个角色。 但我还没有下定决心。
Mmm. Ham or bacon?
嗯。火腿或培根？
- Bacon. - Good. Ham makes me self-conscious.
- 培根。 - 好的。火腿让我自觉。
You're hesitating about having Fay Templeton in your show?
你在犹豫要不要 Fay Templeton 在你的节目中？
You know how those big stars are. Temperamental and hard to get along with.
你知道那些大明星是怎样的。 脾气暴躁，很难相处。
Asking impossible terms and conditions.
问不可能的条件 和条件。
- I'll take my coffee black. - You ought to give in to her.
- 我要黑咖啡。 - 你应该向她屈服。
But, darling, no matter what she asks?
但是，亲爱的， 不管她问什么？
- No matter what she asks. - Why are you so concerned for Templeton?
- 不管她问什么。 - 你为什么这么关心邓普顿？
Oh, I don't care for Templeton. I'm looking out for you.
哦，我不在乎坦普尔顿。 我在找你。
Think what it means for you to have a star like Templeton in your show.
想想拥有对你意味着什么 在你的节目中像坦普尔顿这样的明星。
Mm-hm. Always worried about me, aren't you? Ever think about yourself?
嗯嗯。总是担心我， 你不是吗？有没有想过自己？
Not much lately. Haven't had time.
最近不多。还没来得及。
The minute I saw you without your beard...
见到你的那一刻 没有你的胡子...
...I knew here was a little boy who needed looking after...
...我知道这里有一个小男孩 谁需要照顾...
- ...so I gave myself the job. - Mm-hm.
- ...所以我给了自己这份工作。 - 嗯。
There are a lot of singers, you know, but very few really good looker-afters.
有很多歌手，你知道， 但很少有真正好的照顾者。
GEORGE: Mm-hm.
嗯嗯。
Darling, how would you like a lifetime job of looking after?
亲爱的，你想要怎样 照顾一辈子的工作？
Leading lady, run of the play...
女主，剧中...
...maybe a few heartaches after the curtain goes up...
...也许有些心痛 大幕拉开后……
...but I can guarantee you some laughs.
...但我可以保证 你笑了。
How does it sound?
听起来怎么样？
I think I might like it, Mr. Cohan.
我想我可能会喜欢它，科汉先生。
Could I, uh, see some of the script?
我可以，呃，看看一些剧本吗？
Mm-hm.
嗯嗯。
Hmm.
唔。
Not bad for a first reading.
初读还不错。
The coffee's boiling over.
咖啡沸腾了。
Darling, there's something I forgot to tell you.
亲爱的，有事 我忘了告诉你。
- Yes, dear? - Uh, I gave your song to Templeton tonight.
- 是的亲爱的？ - 呃，今晚我把你的歌给了坦普尔顿。
MARY: Mm-hm.
嗯嗯。
Darling, did you hear me? I, uh...
亲爱的，你听到了吗？我，呃...
I gave your song to Fay Templeton tonight.
我给了你的歌 今晚去费坦普尔顿。
Yes, I know. I knew you did, dear, when you brought the candy and flowers.
是的，我知道。我知道你做到了，亲爱的， 当你带来糖果和鲜花时。
[SINGING] My mother's name was Mary
我母亲的名字是玛丽
She was so good and true
她是如此优秀和真实
Because her name was Mary
因为她的名字叫玛丽
She calls me Mary too
她也叫我玛丽
She wasn't gay or airy
她不是同性恋或通风
But plain as she could be
但她可以很简单
I'd hate to meet a Mary
我不想见到玛丽
Who calls herself Marie
自称玛丽的人
For it was Mary
因为是玛丽
Mary
玛丽
Plain as any name can be
像任何名字一样简单
But with propriety
但有礼貌
Society will say, "Marie"
社会会说，“玛丽”
For it was Mary
因为是玛丽
Mary
玛丽
Long before the fashions came
早在时尚到来之前
And there is something there
那里有东西
That sounds so square
听起来很方正
It's a wonderful song, George, best you've ever done. Itll live for years.
这是一首美妙的歌，乔治，最好的 你曾经做过。它会活好几年。
Thanks, Sam. But I still think Mary should have sung it.
谢谢，山姆。但我还是觉得 玛丽应该唱的。
Oh, that's all right. Fay has the song, but I have the author.
哦，没关系。费有 这首歌，但我有作者。
And there is something there
那里有东西
That sounds so square
听起来很方正
It's a grand
这是一个盛大的
Old
老的
Name
姓名
Only 45 minutes from Broadway
距百老汇仅 45 分钟路程
Think of the changes it brings
想想它带来的改变
For the short time it takes What a difference it makes
在短时间内 它有什么不同
ALL: In the ways of the people and things
在人和事的方式上
Oh, and things
哦，还有事情
Oh, what a fine bunch of Reubens
哦，多么棒的一群鲁本斯
Oh, what a jay atmosphere
哦，多么欢乐的气氛
They have whiskers like hay
他们有像干草一样的胡须
And imagine Broadway Only 45 minutes from here
想象一下百老汇 距离这里仅 45 分钟
It's awfully nice of all you boys To see me to the train
你们所有的男孩都非常好 送我上火车
CHORUS: So long, Mary
久违了，玛丽
I didn't think you'd care If you should never see me again
我没想到你会在意 如果你再也见不到我
CHORUS: You're wrong, Mary
你错了，玛丽
This reminds me of my family
这让我想起了我的家人
On the day I left Schenectady
在我离开斯克内克塔迪的那天
To the depot Then they came with me
到仓库 然后他们和我一起来了
I seem to hear them say
我似乎听到他们说
"So long, Mary"
“再见了，玛丽”
CHORUS: Mary, we will miss you so
玛丽，我们会非常想念你
CHORUS: How we hate to see you go
我们多么讨厌看到你离开
"And we'll all be longing for you, Mary
“我们都会 想念你，玛丽
While you roam"
当你漫游”
ALL: So long, Mary
久违了，玛丽
Don't forget to come back home
别忘了回家
Oh, oh, oh, oh
噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢噢
CHORUS: How we hate to see you go
我们多么讨厌看到你离开
ALL: So long, Mary
久违了，玛丽
Don't forget to come back home
别忘了回家
CHORUS: And we'll all be longing for you, Mary
我们都会 想念你，玛丽
While you're gone
当你走了
ALL: So long, Mary
久违了，玛丽
Don't forget
不要忘记
To come back
要回来
Home
家
MAN [LISPING]: Look at Cohan. He's got them lined up at the box office.
看看科汉。他有他们 在售票处排队。
I've never seen the guy. Got his name all over the place. Look at that.
我从没见过那个人。得到了他的 名满天下。看那个。
"Cohan and Harris present George Washington, Jr.
“科汉和哈里斯出席 小乔治华盛顿
Starring the author and composer, George M. Cohan."
由作者和作曲家主演， 乔治·M·科汉。”
I wonder what the M is for. Oh, modesty.
我想知道M是干什么用的。 哦，谦虚。
- Hello, Mr. Foy. - How are you?
- 你好，福伊先生。 - 你好吗？
- Enjoyed your show last night. - Thank you.
- 昨晚很喜欢你的节目。 - 谢谢。
You always appear in the kind of stuff I like.
你总是出现 在我喜欢的那种东西。
Thank you. That's very nice of you.
谢谢你。你真好。
"George M. Cohan and his royal family.
“乔治·M·科汉 和他的王室。
Books and lyrics, music, and direction by George M. Cohan.
书籍和歌词、音乐和方向 乔治·M·科汉 (George M. Cohan)。
Printed by Sam Divensky."
山姆·迪文斯基印刷。”
That must be Cohan's alias.
那一定是科汉的别名。
Certainly keeps himself in billing, this George M. Cohan.
当然让自己记账， 这个乔治·M·科汉。
Don't memorize that one. There's plenty all over town.
不要记住那个。 全城都有很多。
I'd like to forget it. Say, listen, you connected with this turkey?
我想忘记它。说，听， 你和这只火鸡有联系吗？
Turkey? I hear it's pretty good.
火鸡？听说还不错
It's a malicious rumor to gyp the public.
这是恶意谣言 向公众宣传。
Who is this guy Cohan? Where is he from? What is he, an upstart?
这个科汉是谁？他从哪里来？ 他是什么，暴发户？
Oh, he's been through the mill. Small-time and big-time vaudeville, rep shows.
哦，他经历过磨坊。小时候 和大型杂耍表演，代表节目。
- Even followed dog acts. - Must have looked like an encore.
- 甚至跟随狗的行为。 - 一定看起来像安可。
- Say, uh, is he as good as Foy? - Who?
- 说，呃，他和Foy一样好吗？ - 谁？
Foy, Foy, Eddie Foy.
福伊，福伊，埃迪·福伊。
Oh, pardon me.
哦，原谅我。
Pardon me, I didn't quite catch the name. Would you mind spraying it again?
对不起，我没完全听懂这个名字。 你介意再喷一次吗？
Eddie Foy.
埃迪·福伊。
The star that's got the big show down the street with a chorus of 70.
有大戏的明星 和 70 的合唱在街上。
[LISPING] Why, I thought they looked a little younger than that.
为什么，我以为他们看起来 比那年轻一点。
I hear now that Cohan's in town, Foy's gonna retire.
我现在听说科汉在城里， 福伊要退休了。
Foy won't retire till he's 90.
福伊要到 90 岁才退休。
Is it gonna take him that long to discover he has no talent?
他要花那么长时间吗 发现他没有天赋？
They tell me when he tries to sing, the orchestra puts up umbrellas.
当他试图唱歌时，他们告诉我， 管弦乐队撑起雨伞。
Tries to sing? Why, he's a genius. He keeps his audience glued to the seats.
试着唱歌？为什么，他是个天才。 他让听众紧紧盯着座位。
That's one way of keeping them in the theater. Cohan does it with talent. Look.
这是让他们保持在 剧院。科汉用天赋做到了。看。
Produces his own plays, writes his own books, lyrics and music, plays the leads...
自己创作剧本，自己写剧本 书籍，歌词和音乐，扮演主角......
- ...and is a great dancer. - He dances, eh?
- ...并且是一位出色的舞者。 - 他跳舞，嗯？
When does he get time to practice?
他什么时候有时间练习？
When you write your own plays, you don't have to. Cohan's done all right.
当你写自己的剧本时， 你不必。科汉做得很好。
He's given the world "Yankee Doodle Dandy." What's Foy done for his country?
他给了世界“洋基涂鸦 丹迪。”福伊为他的国家做了什么？
He gave them seven kids.
他给了他们七个孩子。
- Does he dance? - One of the best.
- 他跳舞吗？ - 最好的之一。
When does he get time to practice?
他什么时候有时间练习？
Say, listen, young fella, my name's Eddie Foy.
说，听着，小伙子， 我叫埃迪·福伊。
I know it. I'm George M. Cohan.
我知道。我是乔治·M·科汉。
Oh, so you're Cohan?
哦，所以你是科汉？
Well, if I said anything accidental to make you mad...
好吧，如果我说了什么意外的话 让你生气...
...I want you to know I'm darn glad I did.
...我想让你知道 我很高兴我做到了。
I don't blame you. I'd feel the same way if I were up against Cohan.
我不怪你。我也会有同样的感觉 如果我面对科汉。
- What do like to drink? - Oh, moxie.
- 喜欢喝什么？ - 哦，莫西。
I can supply it. The attraction inside is a whole lot bigger than I am.
我可以提供。里面的吸引力 比我大很多。
Come and see when your show closes.
来看看你的节目什么时候结束。
[SINGING] There's a feeling comes a-stealing And it sets my brain a-reeling
有一种感觉来了-偷 它让我的大脑颤抖
When I listen to the music Of a military band
当我听音乐 军乐队的
Every tune like "Yankee Doodle" Simply sets me off my noodle
每首曲子都像“洋基涂鸦” 简直让我不吃面条
It's that patriotic something That no one can understand
这就是爱国的东西 没有人能理解
CHORUS: Way down south in the land of cotton
在棉花的土地上向南走
Melody untiring
旋律不倦
It's so inspiring
太鼓舞人心了
CHORUS: Hurrah, hurrah We joined the jubilee
万岁，万岁 我们加入了禧年
And that's going some For the Yankees, by gum
这就是一些 对于洋基队，口香糖
Red, white and blue I am for you
红白蓝我为你
Honest, you're a grand old flag
老实说，你是一面伟大的旧旗帜
You're a grand old flag You're a high-flying flag
你是一面伟大的旧旗帜 你是一面高扬的旗帜
And forever in peace may you wave
愿你永远平静地挥手
You're the emblem of
你是象征
The land I love
我爱的土地
ALL: The home of the free and the brave
自由勇敢者的家园
Every heart beats true Under red, white and blue
每颗心都跳动真实 在红色、白色和蓝色下
Where there's never a boast or brag
从来没有吹嘘或吹嘘的地方
ALL: But should old acquaintance be forgot
但是否应该忘记旧相
Keep your eye on that grand old flag
留意那面宏伟的旧旗帜
CHORUS: Rally round the flag Let us rally round the flag
围着国旗集会 让我们团结在旗帜周围
We took the red from the flame of dawn...
我们拿了红 从黎明的火焰...
...the dawn of a new nation.
...一个新国家的黎明。
And the white was the white of the snow at Valley Forge.
而白色就是白色 福吉谷的雪。
The blue was the blue of the free, open sky...
蓝色是蓝色 自由、开阔的天空……
...and the stars were the 13 sisters by the sea...
...而星星是 海边的十三姐妹……
...who built their home and called it liberty.
...谁建造了他们的家 并称之为自由。
CHORUS: To symbolize the spirit
象征精神
Right!
正确的！
CHORUS: The spirit of freedom
自由的精神
Right again!
又对了！
CHORUS: The spirit that gave birth to American
给予的精神 生于美国人
Democracy
民主
That's the spirit!
就是那种精神！
CHORUS: You're a grand old flag
你是一面伟大的旧旗帜
What a grand old flag
多么宏伟的旧国旗
Glory, glory, hallelujah
荣耀，荣耀，哈利路亚
CHORUS: His truth goes marching on
他的真理继续前进
ABRAHAM LINCOLN: And that government...
而那个政府...
...of the people...
……人民……
...for the people, shall not perish...
...为人民， 不会灭亡……
...from the earth.
...来自地球。
CHORUS: When Johnny comes marching home again
当约翰尼再次游行回家时
Hurrah, hurrah
万岁，万岁
We'll give him a hearty welcome then
届时我们将热烈欢迎他
The men will cheer The boys will shout
男人会欢呼 男生会喊
The ladies, they will all turn out
女士们，她们都会出现
And we'll all feel gay When Johnny comes marching home
我们都会感到同性恋 当约翰尼行军回家时
CHORUS: We're one for all and all for one
我们是一个人，一个人
Behind the man Behind the gun
男人的背后 枪的背后
And now that we're in it We're going to win it
现在我们身处其中 我们会赢的
We can't lose a minute There's work to be done
我们不能浪费一分钟 有工作要做
We're with them
我们和他们在一起
United we stand In peace and war
团结就是力量 在和平与战争中
We're with them
我们和他们在一起
We'll fight as we did before
我们会像以前一样战斗
My country 'tis of thee
我的国家是你的
Sweet land of liberty
甜蜜的自由之地
Of thee we sing
我们为你歌唱
ALL: You're a grand old flag You're a high-flying flag
你是一面伟大的旧旗帜 你是一面高扬的旗帜
And forever in peace may you wave
愿你永远平静地挥手
You're the emblem of The land I love
你是象征 我爱的土地
The home of the free and the brave
自由勇敢者的家园
Every heart beats true Under red, white and blue
每颗心都跳动真实 在红色、白色和蓝色下
Where there's never a boast or brag
从来没有吹嘘或吹嘘的地方
But should old acquaintance be forgot
但是否应该忘记旧相
Keep your eye on the grand old flag
密切关注宏伟的旧旗帜
Should old acquaintance be forgot
老相识是否应该被遗忘
Keep your eye on the grand
密切关注宏大
Old
老的
Flag
旗帜
[SINGING] Like the wandering minstrel
像流浪的吟游诗人
I have slouched along the way
一路上我无精打采
Wandering day by day
一天天的流浪
No selection of direction
没有选择方向
Till I heard a lovely voice
直到我听到一个可爱的声音
Which seemed to softly say
似乎在轻声说
Come along with me
跟我一起来
Come along with me away
跟我走
May I have your autograph, Mr. Cohan?
科汉先生，我可以要你的签名吗？
To what do you attribute your continued success, Mr. Cohan?
你归因于什么 你继续成功吗，科汉先生？
Oh, I'm an ordinary guy who knows what ordinary guys like to see.
哦，我是一个普通人谁知道 普通人喜欢看什么。
Front row center, the greatest show on earth, the people.
前排中锋，最大 显示在地球上，人们。
To the people. God bless them.
为人们。上帝保佑他们。
NELLIE: Here, chick, chick, chick.
在这里，小鸡，小鸡，小鸡。
- Here, chick, chick, chick. JOSIE: Heh.
- 在这里，小鸡，小鸡，小鸡。 - 嘿。
Oh, it's such fun, Mother, having cows and chickens.
哦，太有趣了，妈妈， 有牛和鸡。
And everything's running so smoothly.
一切都运行得如此顺利。
Well, it's always been a dream of ours, Mary.
嗯，一直都是 我们的梦想，玛丽。
We kept hoping for 20 years that it might come true someday.
我们一直希望20年 有朝一日它可能会实现。
Imagine knowing how to feed chickens or how much to feed them.
想象一下如何喂鸡 或者喂他们多少。
And you're a farmer only three weeks.
而你是一个只有三周的农民。
Jerry and I have seen a lot of chickens in train windows...
杰瑞和我见过 火车车窗里有很多鸡...
...and we always wanted to raise some of our own.
...我们一直想要 提高我们自己的一些。
You know, watch them hatch and feed them and eat them.
你知道，看着他们孵化 喂它们吃它们。
If we only could. They're so pretty.
如果我们只能。他们真漂亮。
- Georgie? - Yeah?
- 乔治？ - 是的？
- What'd you get Dad for his birthday? - Oh, nothing much. Just a smoking jacket.
- 爸爸生日你送他什么礼物？ - 哦，没什么。只是一件吸烟夹克。
Is it bright? Lots of color? I mean, will he like it?
亮吗？很多颜色？ 我的意思是，他会喜欢吗？
Well, it's silk and very red and very yellow.
嗯，它是丝绸的，很红 而且很黄。
That'll do it. Look what I got him, Georgie.
这样就可以了。 看看我得到了什么，乔治。
Well, now, there's a present. That must have set you back a few.
嗯，现在，有一份礼物。 那一定让你退缩了一些。
Dad needed a new watch.
爸爸需要一块新手表。
His old one's so loud, you can hear it right through his coat.
他的老家伙太吵了，你可以 隔着他的外套就听到了。
My future husband helped me pick it out.
我未来的老公 帮我挑出来。
Your future what?
你的未来是什么？
Husband. We're getting married as soon as Fred's road tour is over.
丈夫。我们要结婚了 弗雷德的公路之旅一结束。
Well...
出色地...
GEORGE: Hm.
嗯。
Little Josie's gonna get married, huh?
小乔西会 结婚吧
Oh, it doesn't seem that long ago...
哦，好像不是很久以前...
Hmm.
唔。
What happens to The Four Cohans?
四个科汉的结局是什么？
Oh, just a simple case of subtraction.
哦，只是一个简单的 减法的情况。
You know, one from four leaves three.
你知道，四分之一的三分之二。
- Three Cohans. - Mm-mm.
- 三个科汉。 - 嗯嗯。
That's only arithmetic.
那只是算术。
One Cohan from four Cohans leaves nothing.
四个中的一个科汉 科汉斯什么也没留下。
Mom and Pop know?
妈妈和爸爸知道吗？
JOSIE: Mm-hm.
嗯嗯。
Mom's been working on the wedding dress for weeks.
妈妈一直在努力 几个星期的婚纱。
What are you thinking about, Georgie?
你在想什么，乔治？
I'm gonna write you the most terrific wedding march ever put on paper.
我会写给你最棒的 婚礼进行曲曾经写在纸上。
It'll pack the pews.
它会收拾长椅。
Say, Dad, will you tell Josie that there's no reason to break up the act?
说，爸爸，你能告诉乔西吗？ 没有理由分手吗？
The Four Cohans are as much an institution as marriage is.
四个科汉人一样多 婚姻是一种制度。
Oh, Georgie, no one knows that any better than I do...
哦，乔治，没人知道 比我做的好...
...but we want to settle down and raise a family.
...但我们想安定下来 并养家糊口。
What's the matter? Can't he raise a family and be a stage manager too?
怎么了？他不能举一个 家庭和舞台经理？
- Hmm? - George.
- 唔？ - 乔治。
George, I'm afraid your mother and I are breaking up the act before Josie is.
乔治，我怕你妈妈和我 在乔西之前分手。
You hear that, Sam? All three of them walking out on me.
你听到了吗，山姆？ 他们三个都向我走来。
There's been a 40-year run, remember?
已经有 40 年的历史了，记得吗？
We're giving you our two weeks' notice, George. Heh.
我们给你我们的两个 几周的通知，乔治。呵呵。
All we'd like to do now is spend the rest of our days here on this farm.
我们现在想做的就是花钱 我们在这个农场的余生。
But you can't do that. You can't put an actor out to grass. Fresh air kills him.
但你不能那样做。你不能放一个 演员出草。新鲜空气要了他的命。
We've gained nearly 10 pounds apiece.
我们每人体重增加了近 10 磅。
You can work it off. The show is ready to go into rehearsal.
你可以解决它。演出 准备进入排练。
There are grand parts in it for both of you.
有宏伟的部分 在其中为你们俩。
No, George, I...
不，乔治，我...
We've had good times together.
我们一起度过了美好的时光。
And, well, new shows need new faces and new feet to go with you.
而且，好吧，新节目需要新面孔 和新的脚与你同行。
From now on, it's just you alone, son.
从现在开始， 只有你一个人，儿子。
JERRY: Well, what's this?
嗯，这是什么？
JOSIE: A surprise, Dad. GEORGE: Happy birthday!
- 一个惊喜，爸爸。 - 生日快乐！
JERRY: For me? Heh. GEORGE: You get your own birthday.
- 为了我？呵呵。 - 你有自己的生日。
JERRY: Look at the size of that one. JOSIE: Make a wish.
- 看看那个的大小。 - 许个愿。
GEORGE: Make your wish. - I have.
- 实现你的愿望。 - 我有。
JOSIE: A good one, Dad.
一个很好的，爸爸。
GEORGE: Which one do you want to open first?
你想先打开哪个？
JOSIE: How about opening this one? Let me help you.
这个怎么开？ 让我来帮助你。
- This one will match your suit, Dad. JERRY: Somebody gave me that last year.
- 这件和你的西装很相配，爸爸。 - 去年有人给了我。
Well, it looks fine.
嗯，看起来不错。
Had it made up on that old backdrop you like so well, fireproofed and everything.
如果它是在那个古老的背景上组成的，你 就像这么好，防火和一切。
Oh, darling, that's a lovely watch. Heh.
哦，亲爱的，这是一个 可爱的手表。呵呵。
I'm so glad you like it, Dad.
我很高兴你喜欢它，爸爸。
This is better than being on next to closing.
这个更好 而不是在关闭旁边。
The only trouble is it's three minutes fast.
唯一的麻烦是它 快三分钟。
Heh-heh. Dad, press the little button on the side and see what happens.
呵呵。爸爸，按下小按钮 在一边，看看会发生什么。
It plays one on one and segues into "Dixie."
它一对一地播放 并进入“Dixie”。
Here's some more ties that you won't like, Jerry.
这里还有一些关系 你不会喜欢的，杰瑞。
I'll have to open up a store, huh? Heh-heh.
我得开一家店，嗯？ 呵呵。
- Oh, uh... - Here's a letter from George.
- 哦，呃... - 这是乔治的一封信。
- Don't open that now... - You haven't written me a letter in 20 years.
- 现在不要打开那个... - 你已经 20 年没有给我写信了。
I'm gonna open it now, and I'm gonna read it.
我现在要打开 我要读它。
George, this isn't your party. Sit down and let him read his letter.
乔治，这不是你的派对。 坐下来，让他读他的信。
"Dear Dad, this is your 62nd birthday, and God bless you.
“亲爱的爸爸，这是你的第 62 生日，愿上帝保佑你。
Maybe I've never told you before, but no son ever had a better dad...
也许我以前从未告诉过你， 但没有儿子有过更好的爸爸……
...or one to be prouder of.
...或者一个值得骄傲的人。
You and mother have always given me more love and understanding...
你和妈妈一直给我 更多的爱和理解……
...than I ever deserved.
...比我应得的。
And all the luck I've had is due to the things you two have taught me.
而我所拥有的所有运气都是应得的 对于你们两个教给我的东西。
Nothing I can do could ever repay the debt.
我无能为力 永远偿还债务。
But here's a little present for you and mother.
但这里有一个小礼物 为你和妈妈。
From this day on, you and I are partners...
从今天开始， 你和我是伙伴...
...in every theater and theatrical property I possess...
...在每个剧院和 我拥有的戏剧财产...
...half and equal.
...一半和相等。
The Cohan Theater, the Astor, the Gaiety...
科汉剧院， 阿斯特，欢乐...
...and the Grand Opera House in Chicago...
...和大歌剧院 芝加哥的房子...
...and all my plays and songs as long as they...
...以及我所有的戏剧和歌曲 只要他们...
...or you and I, live."
……或者你和我，活下去。”
These are not my reading glasses.
这些不是我的老花镜。
Why didn't somebody give me some reading glasses for my birthday?
为什么没有人给我 我生日的老花镜？
"Wish you all my love...
“祝你我所有的爱...
...your son and partner, George."
......你的儿子和伴侣，乔治。”
Well, George, on behalf of your mother and myself, I...
好吧，乔治，代表 你母亲和我自己，我...
There she goes stealing the scene again.
她去那里偷东西 又是那个场景。
GEORGE: One success followed another...
一个成功接踵而至...
...but there was one challenge I hadn't met.
...但有一个挑战 我没见过。
Critics kept saying that musicals and cheap comedies were all I could write.
批评者一直说音乐剧 我只能写廉价喜剧。
I could wave a flag, they said. Nothing else.
他们说，我可以挥动一面旗帜。 没有其他的。
So I wrote a legitimate drama, very deep and very significant.
所以我写了一部合法的戏剧， 非常深刻和非常重要。
No music, no gags, no flag-waving.
没有音乐，没有噱头，没有挥舞旗帜。
I called it Popularity.
我称之为人气。
The title showed how hard I was hoping.
标题显示了如何 我希望很难。
I couldn't attend the opening because I was down the street...
我不能参加开幕式 因为我在街上...
...in The Yankee Prince.
...在洋基王子中。
MAN: Open it up. GEORGE: Keep it closed, Buck.
- 打开它。 - 保持关闭，巴克。
Cohan, you're surely not going to your dressing room now.
科汉，你肯定不会去的 现在去你的更衣室。
You're good for at least another five curtain calls.
你至少适合 又是五次谢幕。
That's enough for tonight.
今晚就够了。
Mr. Cohan, are you sure you're feeling well?
科汉先生，你确定吗 你感觉好吗？
I feel all right. Any news from Popularity?
我觉得没事。 有流行的消息吗？
No, but they should be ringing down just about now.
不，但他们应该是 刚刚响起。
You'd think my family would let me know.
你会认为我的家人 会让我知道。
Well, it's a good sign. They probably couldn't tear themselves away.
嗯，这是一个好兆头。他们大概 无法将自己撕开。
- What time is it? - Seven-thirty.
- 现在是几奌？ - 七点半。
- That clock right? - Yes, sir.
- 那个时钟对吗？ - 是的先生。
That's an early show. They ought to be here by now.
那是早期的节目。 他们现在应该已经到了。
- Maybe something wrong with Mom and Dad. - I've got reports on the minstrel show.
- 也许爸爸妈妈有问题。 - 我有关于吟游诗人表演的报道。
- What'd we lose this week? - Oh, 10,000, more or less.
- 这周我们失去了什么？ - 哦，10,000，或多或少。
- What's the total loss so far? - A few dollars under 200,000.
- 到目前为止的总损失是多少？ - 低于 200,000 的几美元。
Hmm. That include the cost of the red ink?
唔。其中包括 红墨水的成本？
Popularity better be a hit. Got a lot of dough sunk in that too.
人气最好是一击。 也有很多面团沉入其中。
Eddie, call Wallachs and find out what's keeping them.
埃迪，打电话给瓦拉赫斯并找出答案 是什么让他们。
What did the papers say about the minstrel show?
报纸说了什么 关于吟游诗人表演？
Here they are. Rave notices again.
他们来了。 Rave 再次注意到。
Hmm, rave notices. That's bad.
嗯，好评如潮。那很糟。
The better notices you get on minstrel shows, the more it costs you.
你在吟游诗人上得到的通知越多 显示，您花费的越多。
All except the last act. Alecson suggests a new finish.
除了最后一幕。 亚历克森建议一个新的完成。
Hmm, I see. A new finish. Hm.
嗯，我明白了。一个新的结局。嗯。
How about Saturday night?
周六晚上怎么样？
- Close it? - Close it.
- 关闭它？ - 关闭它。
- Saturday night. - Mm-hm.
- 周六晚上。 - 嗯。
- Give the company two weeks' salary. - All right.
- 给公司两周的薪水。 - 好的。
- Oh, good evening, Mrs. Cohan. JERRY: Good evening.
- 哦，晚上好，科汉夫人。 - 晚上好。
- Hello, dear. GEORGE: Hello, Mom. Hi, darling.
- 你好呀。 - 你好，妈妈。嗨，亲爱的。
Dad, I was worried about you. I wondered what happened.
爸爸，我很担心你。 我想知道发生了什么。
Sit down. Right here. You sit down.
坐下。就在这儿。你坐下。
That theater's awfully cold, George. Better have some more heat put in there.
那个剧院太冷了，乔治。 最好多放一些热量在那里。
- Take care of that right away. - Remember that skating act in Camden?
- 马上处理。 - 还记得卡姆登的滑冰表演吗？
They were there. I wonder where they got the money.
他们在那里。 我想知道他们从哪里弄来的钱。
Finnegan, Feeney, and Riley. I remember them well.
芬尼根、菲尼和莱利。 我记得很清楚。
Well, come on, tell me, how'd it go?
好吧，来吧，告诉我，进展如何？
Well, the audience loved it, every minute of it.
好吧，观众喜欢它， 每一分钟。
NELLIE: The sets were beautiful, George.
布景很漂亮，乔治。
Uh...
呃...
Why so quiet, Sam?
为什么这么安静，山姆？
The toughest house I've ever seen.
我见过的最坚固的房子。
The critics walked out at the end of the second act.
批评者在 第二幕结束。
GEORGE: Hmm.
唔。
Mm-hm.
嗯嗯。
Come on, Dad. Come on, let's have it.
来吧，爸爸。来吧，让我们拥有它。
Heh. Well, there's no use beating around the bush.
呵呵。嗯，没用 拐弯抹角。
Pretty bad, George.
很糟糕，乔治。
Could've been a lot better.
本来可以好很多的。
JERRY: All right, you write a bad play. The only thing to do is forget about it.
好吧，你写了一部烂剧本。 唯一能做的就是忘记它。
Everybody's entitled to one failure.
每个人都有权遭受一次失败。
Let's go to Delmonico's, have the party, just as though the show was a hit.
让我们去德尔莫尼科，参加派对， 就好像这个节目很受欢迎一样。
You take the girls on over there, and I'll see you in about a half-hour.
你带女孩去那边， 大约半小时后见。
I've got some things I want to talk over with Sam.
我有一些我想要的东西 和山姆谈谈。
Those critics have been after my blood for years.
那些批评者一直 在我的血之后多年。
They'll gang up on me and do a good job of it, but I'll beat them to it.
他们会联合起来对付我并做好事 它的工作，但我会打败他们。
I'll take an ad in every paper right alongside their reviews...
我会在每份报纸上刊登广告 就在他们的评论旁边......
...telling the public we've got the greatest show in town...
...告诉公众我们有 镇上最伟大的表演......
...sold out for 10 weeks in advance, we'll run a year.
...提前10周售罄， 我们会跑一年。
The public will believe me.
公众会相信我的。
- Listen, Georgie, you can't do that. - Why not?
- 听着，乔治，你不能那样做。 - 为什么不？
Too big a reputation. You can't disappoint the public.
名气太大了。 你不能让公众失望。
They'll never forgive you, never trust you again.
他们永远不会原谅你， 永远不要再相信你了。
We stuck our necks out, and we got clipped.
我们伸出脖子， 我们被剪掉了。
Georgie.
乔治。
You can't do this. You'll always regret it.
你不能这样做。 你永远都会后悔的。
- Sit down and take this. - We'll be sorry.
- 坐下来拿这个。 - 我们会很抱歉。
- To the theater-going public. - George...
- 到剧院的公众。 - 乔治...
To the theater-going public.
献给看戏的公众。
I wrote a play called Popularity.
我写了一部戏，叫《流行》。
Mr. Harris and I produced that play.
哈里斯先生和我制作了那出戏。
In the opinion of people we respect, it is a bad play.
在我们尊重的人看来， 这是一场糟糕的比赛。
In this, we heartily concur.
在这一点上，我们由衷地同意。
It is a very bad play.
这是一部非常糟糕的戏。
I do humbly apologize and ask forgiveness...
我很谦虚地道歉 并请求原谅...
...for having presented anything of which you couldn't possibly approve.
...因为提出了任何 你不可能同意的。
There will be five more performances.
还有五场演出。
Please miss them.
请想念他们。
Signed...
签...
Happy?
快乐的？
It's a wonderful second-act curtain.
这是一个精彩的第二幕幕。
Send copies of this to all the papers for the next edition.
将此副本发送给所有 下一版的论文。
NEWSBOY: Extra! Lusitania torpedoed by German sub!
额外的！卢西塔尼亚 被德国潜艇击沉！
This is it, George.
就是这样，乔治。
And we were worried about the success or failure of a show.
我们担心 一场演出的成败。
Now we've really got something to worry about.
现在我们真的得到了一些东西 担心。
GEORGE: It seems it always happens.
似乎它总是会发生。
Whenever we get too high-hat, too sophisticated for flag-waving...
每当我们戴得太高， 太复杂了，无法挥舞旗帜……
...some thug nation decides we're a pushover, all ready to be blackjacked.
...一些暴徒国家认为我们是 推倒，都准备好被二十一点了。
And it isn't long before we're looking up anxiously...
而且时间不长 在我们焦急地抬头之前……
...to be sure the flag's still waving over us.
...确保国旗的 还在向我们挥手。
MAN 1: Left foot.
左脚。
Right foot.
右脚。
On your toes.
在你的脚趾上。
I used to be a model.
我曾经是一名模特。
You'll look awful pretty peeling potatoes.
你会看起来很漂亮 剥土豆。
- On your way, wise guy. MAN 2: Next.
- 在路上，聪明的家伙。 - 下一个。
MAN 1: Left foot. Right foot.
左脚。右脚。
All right. Take this paper and report to Sergeant Cooper for your examination.
好的。拿着这张纸报告给 库珀中士为您检查。
Next. Name, please. Oh.
下一个。姓名，请。哦。
"George M. Cohan.
“乔治·M·科汉。
Occupation: actor, author, composer, and producer.
职业：演员、作家、 作曲家，制作人。
- Address: Devonshire Hotel." - How do you know so much about me?
- 地址：德文郡酒店。” - 你怎么知道我这么多？
Don't you recognize me, Mr. Cohan? I used to be a clerk at the Friars Club.
你不认识我吗，科汉先生？ 我曾经是修士俱乐部的职员。
- Oh. - Heh-heh. "Age: 39."
- 哦。 - 嘿嘿。 “年龄：39。”
- Doesn't even give me a chance to lie about it. - Thirty-nine? I'm sorry, Mr. Cohan.
- 甚至不给我撒谎的机会。 - 三十九？对不起，科汉先生。
- You're overage. Thirty-one's the limit now. - What's eight or nine years, more or less?
- 你已经超龄了。现在三十一个是极限了。 - 什么是八九年，或多或少？
- The Germans won't ask for a birth certificate. - I know how you feel, Mr. Cohan...
- 德国人不会要求出生证明。 - 我知道你的感受，科汉先生...
...but you've got to be young and tough for this army.
...但你必须年轻 对这支军队来说很艰难。
It's no picnic, all those hardships.
这不是野餐，所有这些艰辛。
The mental strain, the trenches, the fighting, the marching.
精神压力，战壕， 战斗，行军。
MAN 2: And the mademoiselles. - I hope.
- 还有小姐。 - 我希望。
- No, you'll never be able to stand it. - Hardships and physical strain?
- 不，你永远无法忍受。 - 艰辛和身体劳累？
Young man, you don't know what you're talking about.
年轻人，你不知道 你在说什么。
This war's a coffee klatsch compared to a season with a musical show.
这场战争是咖啡klatsch比较 到有音乐表演的季节。
I'd like to see these kids do what I do...
我倒要看看 这些孩子做我做的事...
...in a performance and be on their feet at the finish.
...在表演中 并在终点站起来。
I'll give you an idea of what I mean.
我会让你明白我的意思。
Well, thank you very much for your entertainment, Mr. Cohan...
好的，谢谢 为了您的娱乐，科汉先生...
...but I'm afraid we have more need of you here than over there.
...但恐怕我们还有更多需要 你在这里比那里。
Well, that'll make the war last a year longer.
好吧，那会让战争 持续一年多。
- Good-bye, Mr. Cohan. - Thank you, major. Thank you.
- 再见，科汉先生。 - 谢谢你，少校。谢谢你。
MAN 3: So long. MAN 4: Good-bye.
- 太长。 - 再见。
[SINGING] Johnny, get your gun Get your gun, get your gun
强尼，拿起你的枪 拿起你的枪，拿起你的枪
Take it on the run On the run, on the run
带上它 在奔跑中，在奔跑中
Hear them calling you and me
听到他们呼唤你和我
BOTH: Every son of liberty
每一个自由之子
Hurry, right away! No delay. Go today.
快点，马上！ 没有延迟。今天去。
NORA: Make your daddy glad To have had such a lad
让你爸爸高兴 曾经有过这样的时尚
Tell your sweetheart not to pine
告诉你的爱人不要松
BOTH: To be proud her boy's in line
为她儿子的排队感到自豪
Over there
在那边
Send the word, send the word
送话，送话
That the Yanks are coming
洋基队来了
The drums rum-tumming everywhere
到处都在轰鸣的鼓声
So prepare Say a prayer
所以准备说一个祈祷
Send the word, send the word To beware
送话，送话 要小心
We'll be over We're coming over
我们会结束的 我们过来了
And we won't come back Till it's over over there
我们不会回来 直到它在那边
Over there
在那边
Send the word, send the word Over there
送话，送话
GEORGE: Pick it up, soldier. Keep singing, Nora.
拿起它，士兵。 继续唱歌，诺拉。
MAN 1: Where are the lights? MAN 2: The generator's gone again.
- 灯在哪里？ - 发电机又不见了。
Hit your lights so we can keep going, will ya?
点亮你的灯 所以我们可以继续前进，好吗？
- All right. - Fine, thanks.
- 好的。 - 很好，谢谢。
Hit your lights and keep them on the singer until the others come.
点亮你的灯并保持它们 直到其他人来。
- Certainly. - Fine. Thanks very much.
- 当然。 - 美好的。非常感谢。
CHORUS: That the Yanks are coming
洋基队来了
The drums rum-tumming everywhere
到处都在轰鸣的鼓声
So prepare Say a prayer
所以准备 祈祷
Send the word, send the word To beware
送话，送话 要小心
We'll be over We're coming over
我们会结束的 我们过来了
And we won't come back Till it's over over there
我们不会回来 直到它在那边
Everybody sing!
大家一起唱！
ALL: Over there
在那边
Send the word, send the word
送话，送话
That the Yanks are coming
洋基队来了
The drums rum-tumming everywhere
到处都在轰鸣的鼓声
So prepare
所以准备
Say a prayer
祈祷
Send the word, send the word To beware
送话，送话 要小心
We'll be over
我们会结束的
We're coming over
我们过来了
And we won't come back Till it's over over there
我们不会回来 直到它在那边
GEORGE: We'd won the World War.
我们赢得了世界大战。
Manhattan went wild with postwar hysteria.
曼哈顿疯了 带着战后的歇斯底里。
But I spiked my shows with prewar stuff...
但我加了我的节目 用战前的东西...
...the sentiment and humor an older America had aged in the wood.
......老年人的情感和幽默 美国已经在树林里老化了。
WOMAN [SINGING]: In a kingdom all our own
在我们自己的王国里
With little cupid on the throne
小丘比特在宝座上
With a prince And princess on my knee
与王子 还有我膝盖上的公主
You'll be as happy as can be
你会尽可能快乐
In a love nest
在爱巢里
Cozy and warm
温馨又温暖
Like a dove nest
像鸽子窝
Down on a farm
在农场下
And it's all day long
而且整天都是
They bray
他们叫
Flowers all dripping with dew
花儿都滴着露水
And they join in the chorus Of Nellie Kelly
他们加入合唱团 内莉·凯利
I love you
我爱你
He is the man Who owns Broadway
他是男人 谁拥有百老汇
That's what the daily papers say
日报是这么说的
Oh, where could you find another?
哦，你在哪里可以找到另一个？
I'd like to be shown
我想被展示
Another like Molly Malone
另一个像莫莉马龙
But I love the name Billie
但我喜欢Billie这个名字
My dad's was the same
我爸也是这样
Billie
比莉
GEORGE: Still, it was lonely on the main stem.
不过还是很寂寞 在主干上。
Mother and Josie were gone.
妈妈和乔西走了。
Dad was by himself on the farm and had grown very old.
爸爸一个人在农场 并且已经很老了。
Every night I went to the theater, I expected a phone call.
每天晚上我去剧院， 我期待一个电话。
Well, finally it came.
嗯，终于来了。
You'd better give him two more ccs.
你最好再给他两个cc。
We might as well try to make him as comfortable as possible.
我们不妨尝试使 尽可能让他舒服。
Yes, Dr. Anderson.
是的，安德森博士。
If you have to get back to town, Dr. Llewellyn, I'll be here all night.
如果一定要回城， Llewellyn 博士，我会在这里整晚。
It's all right. I'll wait till George M. gets here from the theater.
没关系。我会等到乔治 M. 从剧院到这里。
- Cigarette, doctor? - Yes, I will.
- 香烟，医生？ - 是的，我会。
Thanks.
谢谢。
I remember I was a kid in medical college in Baltimore...
我记得我还是个孩子 在巴尔的摩医学院...
...when I first saw The Four Cohans.
...当我第一次看到四个科汉时。
They were a great act.
他们是一个伟大的行为。
Yes, they were.
是的，他们是。
I always thought George M.'s sister was the loveliest dancer I'd ever seen.
我一直以为乔治M.的妹妹 是我见过的最可爱的舞者。
Can't help thinking a theatrical era is dying in there.
忍不住想一个戏剧时代 死在那里。
His sister and his mother gone and now the old man.
他的姐姐和他的母亲走了 现在是老人。
In some ways, I think he was the best performer of the lot.
在某些方面，我认为他是 最好的表演者。
Well, I'd settle for his age.
好吧，我会适应他的年龄。
There never was anything dull about his life, either.
从来没有什么无聊的事 关于他的生活，要么。
And he's lived to see his son an American institution.
他活着见到他的儿子 美国的一个机构。
Yeah.
是的。
I'd settle for that too.
我也愿意接受。
DOCTOR: Hello, Mr. Cohan.
你好，科汉先生。
- How is he? - Resting quietly.
- 他怎么样？ - 安静地休息。
Oh. I see.
哦。我懂了。
I think you'd better go in alone.
我想你最好一个人进去。
We can't... We can't do that.
我们不能……我们不能那样做。
Wait till George gets here. Where's George?
等到乔治来了。 乔治在哪里？
Here I am, Dad. Here I am.
我在这里，爸爸。我在这里。
Oh, that's good. I'm glad you came.
哦，这是个好。非常高兴你来了。
The booking office has been calling up all day...
订票处 一整天都在打电话……
...and they want us to play Des Moines the last half of the week.
......他们想让我们玩Des Moines 上半周。
Don't worry about that. We're not going to. I've canceled it.
别担心。 我们不会。我已经取消了。
We can pick it up on the way back.
我们可以在回来的路上捡起它。
- How did it go tonight? Mmm. - Oh, fine. Fine. Yeah.
- 今晚过得怎么样？嗯。 - 哦，好吧。美好的。是的。
It's not every kid gets that gets the chance to play Peck's bad boy.
不是每个孩子都能得到 有机会扮演派克的坏小子。
That's right.
这是正确的。
Were you? Were you nervous? Did you remember your lines?
你是……？你紧张吗？ 你还记得你的台词吗？
Oh, sure. Every one.
行，可以。每个人。
- "I can lick any kid in town." - Heh. Good.
- “我可以舔镇上的任何孩子。” - 嘿。好的。
Now, don't you upstage your mother, or I'll whale the tar out of you.
现在，你不要抢了你妈妈的风头， 否则我会把焦油从你身上榨干。
Don't worry, Dad. I'll never do that.
别担心，爸爸。我永远不会那样做。
I'll play the whole show with one foot in the trough.
我会播放整个节目 一只脚在槽中。
No, no, no. We've been billed as The Four Cohans.
不不不。我们一直 被称为“四个科汉”。
You're not gonna break up the act.
你不会破坏演出的。
Don't worry, Dad. They never will.
别担心，爸爸。他们永远不会。
We won't let them. Won't let them.
我们不会让他们。不会让他们。
JERRY: How many curtain calls did you take tonight?
多少次谢幕 你今晚拍了吗？
GEORGE: Six. Six curtains.
六。六帘。
- That's pretty good for a drama. - Yeah.
- 这对戏剧来说很不错。 - 是的。
- Did you make a speech? - Mm-hm. I thanked them for us.
- 你演讲了吗？ - 嗯。我为我们感谢他们。
I said, "My mother thanks you...
我说：“我妈妈谢谢你...
...my father thanks you...
...我父亲谢谢你...
...my sister thanks you...
……姐姐谢谢你……
[SOBBING] ...and I thank you.
......我谢谢你。
GEORGE: Well...
出色地...
...it was a good combination, Sam, worked well for a long time.
...这是一个很好的组合，山姆， 很长一段时间运作良好。
Yeah, now that it's all over, who was the senior partner...
是的，现在一切都结束了， 谁是高级合伙人...
...and who was the junior partner?
......谁是初级合伙人？
You mean, who was Dietz and who was Goff?
你是说，迪茨是谁 高夫是谁？
Well, I bet it's the first firm in the history of show business had two senior partners.
好吧，我敢打赌它是历史上第一家公司 演艺界有两位资深合伙人。
Well, uh, you know how I feel, don't you, Sam?
嗯，你知道我的感受， 不是吗，山姆？
Sure. I understand.
当然。我明白。
You know, when Dad died, with him went the last link with The Four Cohans.
你知道，当爸爸去世的时候，和他一起去了 与四个科汉的最后一个链接。
All the backslapping and the applause, well, it became unimportant.
所有的掌声和掌声， 好吧，它变得不重要了。
No more fun in it.
没有更多的乐趣。
It didn't mean anything anymore with Dad, Mom and Josie gone.
这不再意味着什么 爸爸、妈妈和乔西走了。
So Mary and I are going away and enjoy ourselves...
所以玛丽和我要走了 并享受我们自己...
...and visit places we've always wanted to see...
...并参观地方 我们一直想看...
...old theaters where nobody ever even heard of us.
...没有人的老剧院 甚至听说过我们。
You'll have to go to Timbuktu.
你必须去廷巴克图。
We've got it booked.
我们已经订好了。
George, you've always been the one with the words.
乔治，你一直都是 带字的那个。
I never was much of a hand at saying things.
我从来都不是一手好牌 在说事情。
But we've done more than make a lot of money...
但我们做得更多 比赚很多钱...
...and lose a little.
……损失一点。
Sometimes friends drift apart. Let's not let that happen to us.
有时朋友会分道扬镳。 让我们不要让这种事情发生在我们身上。
No matter how legal the dissolution of this partnership is, Sam...
无论解散多么合法 这种伙伴关系是，山姆...
...50 percent of me will always be here in this office.
...50%的人会 永远待在这个办公室。
I'll remember that when the rent comes due.
我会记住的 房租到期时。
You'll be more successful than ever.
你会比以往任何时候都更成功。
But if ever the rent does come due and you can't meet it, well, you know...
但如果租金真的到期了 你不能满足它，好吧，你知道...
...and by the same token, if I get stuck in Madagascar...
...出于同样的原因， 如果我被困在马达加斯加...
Heh-heh. -- you'll hear from me.
呵呵。 ...你会听到我的消息。
You'd better get out of here.
你最好离开这里。
That ship will sail without you.
那艘船将在没有你的情况下航行。
- Seasick pills. - Mm-hm.
- 晕船药。 - 嗯。
SAM: I won't go to the boat with you.
我不会和你一起上船的。
You know how red my nose gets.
你知道我的鼻子有多红。
What's this? We thought you guys weren't speaking to each other.
这是什么？我们以为你们 没有互相说话。
Can we have a picture of you tearing up your contract?
我们可以有一张照片吗 你撕毁你的合同？
That's impossible. We never had a written contract.
这不可能。 我们从来没有书面合同。
The only contract we've ever had.
我们唯一的合同。
Hold that pose. We want to show it to our legal department.
保持那个姿势。我们想 出示给我们的法律部门。
Shoot it, boys.
开枪吧，孩子们。
GEORGE: Life was less full, but it was by no means empty.
生活不那么充实，但它 绝不是空的。
I still had Mary, a playmate as well as a helpmate.
我还有玛丽， 一个玩伴，也是一个帮手。
We set out to rubberneck at the world.
我们开始了 在世界。
Nelson monument. It's a good thing I wasn't born an Englishman.
纳尔逊纪念碑。这是一件好事 我不是天生的英国人。
With the history their flag has, I'd have waved myself to death.
凭借他们的旗帜所拥有的历史， 我会挥手致死。
Oh, George, I didn't know you could yodel.
哦，乔治， 我不知道你可以约德尔。
Learned it on the farm. Nothing but hog-calling with frost on it.
在农场学的。 什么都没有，只是在上面结霜。
It takes two men to impersonate a horse on Broadway.
冒充两个男人 百老汇的一匹马。
And you always have trouble casting the front end.
而你总是有麻烦 铸造前端。
GEORGE: But folks always come back to where their heart is...
但人们总会回来 他们的心在哪里……
...so we came back to the farm...
...所以我们回到了农场...
...the farm we Cohans had dreamed of when farmers were envying us.
...我们科汉斯梦寐以求的农场 农民嫉妒我们的时候。
Hey, mister, our radiator needs some H2O. Can we use your well?
嘿，先生，我们的散热器需要一些 H20。 我们可以用你的井吗？
Sure, go ahead. Help yourselves.
好，去吧。请自便。
Come on, Jack. Let's make this hop-up solid.
来吧，杰克。 让我们把这个跳起来扎实。
Okay, Jackson, come on. This isn't any free jitney.
好的，杰克逊，来吧。 这不是任何免费的jitney。
GEORGE: Radiator busted?
散热器坏了？
Nah. It's only got high blood pressure.
不。它只有得到 高血压。
What are you gonna do about tires if those give out?
你打算怎么处理轮胎 如果那些放弃？
Oh, it'll run a lot smoother on the rims.
哦，它会运行很多 轮辋上更光滑。
"Stix nix hix pix."
“Stix nix hix pix。”
Greek. I'll bet that's Greek talk.
希腊语。我敢打赌那是希腊语。
BOY: That ain't Greek. That's Swedish or Russian. Stix nix hix pix.
那不是希腊语。那是瑞典语 或俄语。 Stix nix hix pix。
That's show business talk. Here, I'll translate it for you.
那是演艺界的谈话。 在这里，我给你翻译一下。
"Stix," small towns, "nix," refuse, "hix," rube, "pix," pictures.
“Stix”，小镇，“nix”，垃圾， “hix”、“rube”、“pix”图片。
"Small towns refuse rube pictures." Stix nix hix pix.
“小城镇拒绝粗俗的图片。” Stix nix hix pix。
- Stix nix hix pix.
- Stix nix hix pix。
BOTH [SINGING]: A-stix a-nix hix a-pix
A-stix a-nix hix a-pix
A-stix a-nix hix pix
A-stix a-nix hix pix
- I thought that was new jive talk. - New what talk?
- 我以为那是新的谈话。 - 新谈什么？
- Jive talk. - Oh.
- 胡说八道。 - 哦。
- Are you an actor, sir? GEORGE: Used to be.
- 你是演员吗，先生？ - 以前是。
- What were some of your pictures? - Not in pictures.
- 你的一些照片是什么？ - 不在图片中。
I was on Broadway in the legitimate theater.
我在百老汇 在合法的剧院。
Oh. What's your name, sir?
哦。先生，您叫什么名字？
- Cohan. - Cohen?
- 科汉。 - 科恩？
Cohan. George M. Cohan.
科汉。乔治·M·科汉。
BOY: You must have been before our time. - Yes, guess I was.
- 你一定早于我们的时代。 - 是的，我猜我是。
Were you ever in some big shows?
你参加过一些大型演出吗？
- Yeah, a few. - Like what?
- 是的，有几个。 - 像什么？
Oh, uh, like, uh, Little Nellie Kelly.
哦，呃，像，呃， 小妮莉凯莉。
- The Tavern. Ah, Wilderness! - Uh-uh.
- 酒馆。啊，荒野！ - 嗯嗯。
Mmm. Raised in a vacuum bottle.
嗯。在真空瓶中长大。
Well, I guess your parents must have seen me, uh, fathers and mothers.
嗯，我猜你父母一定有 见过我，呃，父亲和母亲。
BOY: Maybe they have. I never heard them talk about it.
也许他们有。我从不 听到他们谈论它。
Have you ever heard a song called, uh, "Give My Regards to Broadway"?
你有没有听过一首歌叫，呃， “向百老汇致敬”？
- I don't think so. - Mmm. No, sir. Who sang it?
- 我不这么认为。 - 嗯。不，先生。谁唱的？
- Who sang it? GIRL: Oh, was it a theme song or something?
- 谁唱的？ - 哦，是主题曲还是什么？
- Did that follow "Beat Me Daddy, 8 to the Bar"? - Yes! Or "Jeepers Creepers."
- 那是在“Beat Me Daddy, 8 to the Bar”之后吗？ - 是的！或“Jeepers Creepers”。
ALL [SINGING]: Jeepers creepers
吉普车爬行者
Where'd you get those peepers?
你从哪儿弄来的那些偷窥者？
Where'd you get those eyes?
你哪来的那双眼睛？
Come on, kids. Time's a-wasting.
来吧，孩子们。时间是浪费。
Well, we gotta scram now. Swinging session.
好吧，我们现在得滚了。 摇摆会议。
Thank you very much, mister... What was your name again?
非常感谢您，先生... 你又叫什么名字？
Cohan. George Cohan.
科汉。乔治·科汉。
Good-bye, Georgie.
再见，乔治。
You're cute!
你很可爱！
BOY: Nice old guy. We gotta get to that session, let's go.
不错的老家伙我们必须得到 到那个会议，我们走吧。
Come on, we got places to go and things to do.
来吧，我们有地方 去和要做的事情。
GIRLS: Bye!
再见！
They did that.
他们这样做了。
I'm not angry, but it is very discouraging.
我没有生气， 但这非常令人沮丧。
Kid asked me my name, and I said Cohan. He asked me again, and I said Cohan.
孩子问我的名字，我说科汉。 他又问我，我说科汉。
Hm. Never even heard of me. Sixteen years old, and I bet you he can't read.
嗯。甚至从未听说过我。十六 岁，我敢打赌他不会读书。
But you've been away from that theater for years, George. Years.
但你已经远离那个 剧院多年，乔治。年。
Nine or 10 generations have grown up since then.
九代或十代 从那时起就长大了。
Naturally, they don't remember you. Nobody's got that good a memory.
自然，他们不记得你。 没有人有那么好的记忆力。
Why not? Many generations remembered my father and mother in vaudeville.
为什么不？几代人都记得 我的父亲和母亲在杂耍表演中。
That's because they were real troupers. They stayed with it.
那是因为他们是真正的马戏团。 他们坚持了下来。
Your father could do a buck-and-wing when he was 60 years old.
你父亲可以做一个逆向而行 在他60岁的时候。
- What makes you think I can't? - I'd hate to see you try it.
- 是什么让你认为我做不到？ - 我不想看到你试一试。
Your father never sat around an orchard listening to his arteries hardening.
你父亲从不围坐在果园旁 听他的动脉硬化。
- Nothing the matter with my arteries. - No, not right now...
- 我的动脉没有问题。 - 不，不是现在……
...because those kids got you all worked up.
...因为那些孩子 让你们都辛苦了。
You're picking on me for a reason, Mary.
你在挑剔我 出于某种原因，玛丽。
You're trying to get a rise out of me. Come on, let's have it. What is it?
你试图让我振作起来。 来吧，让我们拥有它。它是什么？
All right. Here it is.
好的。这里是。
I got a long-distance call from Sam Harris this afternoon.
我接到一个长途电话 今天下午山姆哈里斯。
What about?
关于什么？
He's producing a new show by Kaufman and Hart.
他正在制作一个新节目 考夫曼和哈特。
They're good writers. Nothing I could do to improve their stuff.
他们是好作家。 我无能为力来改善他们的东西。
Sam thinks you could, if you played the lead.
山姆认为你可以， 如果你发挥领先。
Play the lead? Now, what is the matter with that man?
发挥主导作用？现在，什么是 那个男人的事？
Hasn't he got any sense at all? What's he trying to do, spoil our fun?
他难道一点意思都没有吗？ 他想做什么，破坏我们的乐趣？
But are you having fun, George?
但是你玩得开心吗，乔治？
When we were in Europe, you haunted every theater...
我们在欧洲的时候， 你闹鬼了每一个剧院...
...not knowing a word that was said onstage.
...不知道一个字 这是在台上说的。
Going back, congratulating the actors...
回去， 恭喜演员...
They didn't even know what you were talking about.
他们甚至不知道什么 你说的。
-- just to smell that greasepaint again.
...只是闻到那个味道 再次油彩。
You think I'm stagestruck.
你认为我是舞台剧。
The only reason I ever go near a theater is to get out of the night air.
我曾经靠近过的唯一原因 剧院是为了摆脱夜晚的空气。
Fun? I'm having a wonderful time.
乐趣？我玩得很开心。
I have nothing to do with Broadway.
我与百老汇无关。
Sam says it's a great part, no other actor in the world but you could do it.
山姆说这是一个很棒的部分，没有其他的 世界上的演员，但你可以做到。
That's just some more of that Harris con.
这只是更多 那个哈里斯骗局。
He needs me about as much as he needs a hole in the head.
他同样需要我 因为他需要在头上打个洞。
He really does need you, George. He's in trouble.
他真的需要你，乔治。 他有麻烦了。
If positions were reversed, he'd help you out. You know he would.
如果位置颠倒，他会提供帮助 你出去。你知道他会的。
Besides, he never said so, but Sam's broke.
而且，他从来没有说过， 但山姆破产了。
Can you think of any more reasons?
你还能想出更多的理由吗？
Yes. I want you to.
是的。我要你去。
Well, that settled it.
嗯，这就解决了。
I've never refused you anything, have I?
我从来没有拒绝过你 什么，我有吗？
We do it. Come on, let's get packing.
我们这样做。来吧，我们去收拾行李。
We're all packed.
我们都挤满了。
What?
什么？
We're all packed, dear.
我们都挤满了，亲爱的。
Now you can start getting mad all over again...
现在你可以开始获取 又疯了……
...because I told Sam I'd talk you into it.
...因为我告诉山姆 我会说服你的。
What are you laughing about?
你在笑什么？
Just full of news, aren't you? Telling me all kinds of things, huh?
只是充满了新闻，不是吗？ 告诉我各种各样的事情，嗯？
Well, I want you to know I knew it all the time.
好吧，我想让你知道 我一直都知道。
I was listening in on the phone downstairs while you were talking to Sam.
我在楼下听电话 当你和山姆说话的时候。
Why, you devil. You knew it all the time!
为什么，你这个恶魔。 你一直都知道！
And what's more, I phoned Sam right back and told him I'd play it.
更重要的是，我给山姆打了电话 马上回来告诉他我会玩。
Oh, I ought to pop you.
哦，我应该弹出你。
- You... You... - Heh-heh-heh. Oh!
- 你……你…… - 嘿嘿嘿。哦！
- Oh.
- 哦。
[SINGING] It's really a wonderful job
这真的是一个很棒的工作
For fellows like George, Abe and me too
对于像乔治这样的人， 安倍和我也是
It's great to shake hands with a mob
和一群人握手真是太好了
And to hold every kid on your knee too
并抱着每一个孩子 在你的膝盖上
Every word that I speak Goes into headlines
我说的每一句话 登上头条
When I speak All the papers hold their deadlines
当我说话 所有论文都有截止日期
But I have found a way Of dropping a hint
但我找到了一种方法 暗示
Or a glint of the truth That the boys cannot print
或者真相的闪光 男孩们不能打印
For instance
例如
When I was courting Eleanor
当我向埃莉诺求爱时
I told her Uncle Teddy I wouldn't run for president
我告诉她泰迪叔叔 我不会竞选总统
Unless the job was steady
除非工作稳定
Don't print it Strictly off the record
不要打印它 严格记录在案
We entertained the royalty But we were never flustered
我们招待了皇室成员 但我们从不慌张
We gave them Yankee hot dogs With Colman's English Mustard
我们给了他们洋基热狗 配科尔曼的英国芥末
Don't print it Strictly off the record
不要打印它 严格记录在案
It's pleasant at the White House But I'll tell you how I feel
在白宫很愉快 但我会告诉你我的感受
The food is simply terrible Just sauerkraut and veal
食物简直太糟糕了 只有酸菜和小牛肉
If Mrs. R. would stay at home I'd get a decent meal
如果 R 夫人留在家里 我会得到一顿像样的饭菜
But that's off the record
但这不是记录
When I go up to Hyde Park
当我去海德公园时
It's not for just the ride there
这不仅仅是为了在那里兜风
It's not that I like Hyde Park
不是我喜欢海德公园
But I love to park and hide there
但我喜欢停车躲在那里
Don't print it It's strictly off the record
不要打印它 这是严格记录在案的
I sit up in my study Writing gags for Mr. Ickes
我坐在书房里 为 Ickes 先生写笑话
And insults for the gentlemen
以及对绅士的侮辱
Who'd love to slip him Mickeys
谁愿意让他滑倒米奇
Don't print that Off the record
不要打印那个 关闭记录
I scrapped the Prohibition Act When we required a bracer
我废除了禁酒令 当我们需要护腕时
And finished up the Boulder Dam To give the boys a chaser
并完成了博尔德水坝 给男孩一个追逐者
Don't print it It's strictly off the record
不要打印它 这是严格记录在案的
And for my friends in Washington Who complain about the taxes
对于我在华盛顿的朋友 谁抱怨税收
Who cares as long as we can knock The ax out of the Axis?
谁在乎只要我们能敲门 轴心国的斧头？
Don't print it It's strictly off the record
不要打印它 这是严格记录在案的
I can't forget how Lafayette Helped give us our first chance
我不能忘记老佛爷 帮助我们获得了第一次机会
To win our fight for liberty And now they've taken France
赢得我们为自由而战 现在他们占领了法国
We'll take it back from Hitler And put ants in his Ja-pants
我们会从希特勒手中夺回它 把蚂蚁放在他的日本裤里
And that's for the record
这是为了记录
Good work, kids. I'll see you at 11 in the morning.
干得好，孩子们。我会明白的 你早上11点。
And then came your wire, and I was really worried.
然后是你的电报， 我真的很担心。
Well, here I am going on like Tennyson's book, giving you the story of my life.
好吧，我在这里像丁尼生一样继续 书，给你我的生活故事。
I'm sorry. You should've stopped me.
对不起。你应该阻止我的。
Why, I wanted to hear the story of your life.
为什么，我想听 你的人生故事。
It has a direct bearing on my sending for you.
它有一个直接的轴承 在我为你发送。
Do you know what this is?
你知道这是什么吗？
The Congressional Medal of Honor.
国会荣誉勋章。
Let's see what the inscription says.
让我们看看铭文是怎么说的。
I congratulate you, Mr. Cohan.
我祝贺你，科汉先生。
I understand you're the first person of your profession to receive this honor.
我明白你是第一个人 你的职业获得这个荣誉。
You should be very proud.
你一定很自豪吧。
Oh, I am proud.
哦，我很自豪。
In fact, I'm flabbergasted.
事实上，我大吃一惊。
First time in my life, I'm speechless.
人生第一次， 我无语了。
Uh... You're sure there isn't some mistake?
呃...你确定在那里 是不是有些错误？
Quite sure.
非常肯定。
This medal is for people who've given their lives for their country or done something big.
这枚奖章是给那些付出过自己的人的 为自己的国家而活或做过大事。
I'm just a song-and-dance man. Everybody knows that.
我只是一个唱歌跳舞的人。 每个人都知道这一点。
A man may give his life to his country in many different ways, Mr. Cohan.
一个人可以为他的国家献出生命 在许多不同的方面，科汉先生。
And quite often, he isn't the best judge of how much he has given.
而且很多时候，他不是最好的法官 他给了多少。
Your songs were a symbol of the American spirit.
你的歌是一个象征 的美国精神。
"Over There" was just as powerful a weapon as any cannon...
“那边”同样强大 像任何大炮一样的武器...
...as any battleship we had in the first World War.
...就像我们拥有的任何战舰一样 在第一次世界大战中。
Today, we're all soldiers. We're all on the front.
今天，我们都是军人。 我们都在前线。
We need more songs to express America.
我们需要更多的歌曲 表达美国。
I know you and your comrades will give them to us.
我认识你和你的战友 会把它们交给我们。
Mr. President, I've just begun to earn this medal.
总统先生，我刚刚 开始获得这枚勋章。
It's quite a thing.
这是一件大事。
Well, it's the best material we could find, what with priorities and all.
嗯，这是我们最好的材料 可以找到，有什么优先事项和所有。
Good-bye, sir.
再见，先生。
And I want you to know that I'm not the only one that's grateful.
我想让你知道 我不是唯一一个感激的人。
My mother thanks you, my father thanks you...
妈妈谢谢你 我父亲谢谢你...
...my sister thanks you, and I assure you, I thank you.
……我姐姐谢谢你， 我向你保证，我感谢你。
And, uh, I wouldn't worry about this country if I were you.
而且，呃，我不会担心 如果我是你，关于这个国家。
We've got this thing licked.
我们已经解决了这个问题。
Where else could a plain guy like me come in and talk things over with the head man?
像我这样的普通人还能从哪里来 进去和头人商量一下？
Well, that's about as good a definition of America...
嗯，差不多一样好 美国的定义...
...as any I've ever heard.
……就像我听过的一样。
Good-bye, Mr. Cohan, and good luck.
再见，科汉先生，祝你好运。
Good-bye, sir, and good luck to you.
再见，先生，祝你好运。
CROWD [SINGING]: Over there
在那边
Send the word, send the word
送话，送话
That the Yanks are coming
洋基队来了
The drums rum-tumming everywhere
到处都在轰鸣的鼓声
So prepare Say a prayer
所以准备 祈祷
Send the word, send the word To beware
送话，送话 要小心
We'll be over
我们会结束的
We're coming over
我们过来了
And we won't come back Till it's over
我们不会回来 直到结束
What's the matter, old-timer? Don't you remember this song?
怎么了，老铁？ 你不记得这首歌了吗？
Seems to me I do.
在我看来，我愿意。
Well, I don't hear anything.
好吧，我什么也没听到。
Send the word over there
把话传到那边
That the Yanks are coming
洋基队来了
The drums rum-tumming everywhere
到处都在轰鸣的鼓声
So prepare Say a prayer
所以准备 祈祷
Send the word, send the word To beware
送话，送话 要小心
We'll be over We're coming over
我们会结束的 我们过来了
And we won't come back Till it's over over there
我们不会回来 直到它在那边